[Music]
[音樂]
maybe it's the way you say my
也許這就是你說我的方式
name
姓名
[Music]
[音樂]
maybe it's the way you play your game
也許這就是你玩遊戲的方式
but it's so good i've never known
但它是如此的好，我從來不知道
anybody like you
像你這樣的人
but it's so good i've never dreamed of
但這太好了我做夢也沒想到
[Music]
[音樂]
of a love nobody comes once in a
沒有人來過一次
lifetime
壽命
and i'm pretty sure that you are that
我很確定你就是那個
love of mine
我的愛
[Music]
[音樂]
i see forever in your eyes
我永遠在你眼裡
i think that you are the one for me
我認為你是我的唯一
[Music]
[音樂]
cause it gets so
因為它變得如此
hard to
難以
breathe
呼吸
when you're looking at me
當你看著我
i've never felt so alive and free
我從未感到如此活躍和自由
i've never felt so happy
我從未感到如此快樂
[Music]
[音樂]
and i'm pretty sure that you are that
我很確定你就是那個
love of mine
我的愛
[Music]
[音樂]
my
我的
smiles
微笑
[Music]
[音樂]
praying to god that one day you'll be
祈禱上帝有一天你會成為
mine wishing on dandelions
我在蒲公英上許願
[Music]
[音樂]
my darling know that
我親愛的知道
i'm in a field
我在一個領域
[Music]
[音樂]
i feel okay when i
我感覺很好
see you smile
見你笑
[Music]
[音樂]
all of
所有的
wishing on everyone that you would be
希望每個人都成為你
mine
礦
[Music]
[音樂]
ah
啊
hold on uh can you guys hear me
等等，你們能聽到我說話嗎
i
一世
i really don't know how
我真的不知道怎麼做
good i sound with this new microphone
很好，我用這個新麥克風聽起來不錯
but hey
但是嘿
hello
你好
oh can you hear me like
哦，你能聽到我的聲音嗎
is it coming through like one ear
它像一隻耳朵一樣穿過嗎
uh let me see
呃讓我看看
if i go over here
如果我去這裡
can you guys hear me on the other ear
你們能聽到我的另一隻耳朵嗎
tail
尾巴
oh my god that's so cool
哦，天哪，太酷了
dude that's so cool holy [ __ ]
伙計，這太酷了神聖[__]
oh boy
好傢伙
i'm gonna have a lot of fun tonight
今晚我會玩得很開心
it's a tad bit quiet it's a bit quiet
有點安靜 有點安靜
maybe i can fix that
也許我可以解決這個問題
do i sound uh
我聽起來呃
should i be louder hold on i don't know
我應該大聲點堅持嗎我不知道
wait a second yeah
等一下是的
[Music]
[音樂]
oh i might have to mute the uh alerts
哦，我可能不得不靜音呃警報
for this stream right hold on give me a
對於這條流，請稍等，給我一個
second
第二
hold on one second there we go
等一下，我們開始
a little bit louder
大聲一點
it sounds fine to you
聽起來不錯
uh
呃
yeah let me think
是的，讓我想想
yeah this is the first time i'm ever
是的，這是我第一次
doing this so uh any kind of help would
這樣做，任何幫助都會
be really appreciated guys sorry
真的很感激伙計們對不起
i'm kind of nervous honestly um i don't
老實說，我有點緊張，我不
know if
知道是否
i'm actually really nervous about this
我真的很緊張
but uh hold on let me let me try uh
但是，等等，讓我讓我試試，呃
putting my
把我的
i wonder if you guys can hear this let
我想知道你們能不能聽到這個讓
me put my uh
我把我的呃
my microphone to my chest maybe you can
我的麥克風在我的胸前也許你可以
hear my heartbeat
聽到我的心跳
wait can you actually hear it
等等，你真的能聽到嗎
you can oh my god
你可以哦，我的上帝
wow that's really cool
哇，這真的很酷
dude
老兄
wow
哇
that's so cool holy [ __ ]
太酷了神聖[__]
but i hope you're having a good morning
但我希望你早上好
so far guys uh my heart's being fast
到目前為止，伙計們，我的心跳很快
yeah it is because uh you know i'm a
是的，因為你知道我是
little i'm a little nervous just just a
小我有點緊張只是一個
tad bit
一點點
so you might um i might be a little
所以你可能嗯我可能有點
clumsy today but uh
今天很笨拙但是呃
you guys will treat me
你們會對待我的
right
正確的
i don't know what to say
我不知道該說些什麼
i feel like i feel like it's like
我覺得我覺得就像
um
嗯
what's it it's like i'm on a i'm on a
這是什麼就像我在一個我在一個
first date or something like that i
第一次約會或類似的事情我
guess so it's i'm trying my best to uh
猜猜所以我正在盡我最大的努力
stay composed but oh my god uh i feel so
保持鎮靜，但我的天啊，我感覺如此
uh i feel so frazzled
呃，我感到很疲憊
um
嗯
louder you want me to go louder okay
大聲點你想讓我大聲點好嗎
hold on
堅持，稍等
let me try but what if i get
讓我試試，但如果我得到了怎麼辦
maybe you guys would like if i try and
如果我嘗試一下，也許你們會喜歡
did this uh
做這個呃
is this loud enough am i uh
這聲音夠大嗎？
am i close enough
我離得夠近嗎
tell me to get
告訴我得到
did closer work i don't know
做了更密切的工作我不知道
a little closer
更近一點
that sounds great okay
聽起來不錯
oh that's so good all right
哦，那太好了
that makes me happy all right
這讓我很開心
you might be able to hear a little bit
你也許能聽到一點
of my background and like my clicks but
我的背景，喜歡我的點擊，但
i hope that doesn't bother anybody
我希望這不會打擾任何人
um
嗯
balbae oh
巴爾巴哦
bow bae you guys are my palpate
鞠躬，你們是我的觸角
okay
好的
um
嗯
let me try moving to the uh other ear
讓我試著移到呃另一隻耳朵
till
直到
hold on
堅持，稍等
let me give this side some love as well
讓我也給這邊一些愛吧
is that good till
是不是很好直到
oh you're so cute you guys are so cute
哦，你真可愛，你們真可愛
i don't know about uh i don't know why
我不知道 呃 我不知道為什麼
you're calling me the cute one you guys
你們叫我可愛的你們
are
是
even more adorable
更可愛
oh what to do what to do with you
哦 怎麼辦 怎麼辦
all right
好的
yeah i think it's fine i just gotta get
是的，我認為這很好，我只需要得到
a little bit uh
有點呃
a little bit closer
稍微靠近一點
maybe a little closer
也許更近一點
if this is comfortable right
如果這很舒服
sorry you have to forgive me it's my
對不起，你必須原諒我，這是我的
first time so i'm i'm i'm really nervous
第一次所以我我真的很緊張
i'm not lying though this is really my
我沒有說謊，雖然這真的是我的
first time trying to do something like
第一次嘗試做類似的事情
this
這
uh i'll try my best to uh that's it
呃，我會盡力的，呃，就是這樣
i'll try my best to um read some of the
我會盡力去讀一些
donations to on the
捐贈給
stream labs so i can
流實驗室，所以我可以
properly uh take some i don't know if
正確的呃拿一些我不知道是否
you guys want me you want me to say
你們想要我 你想要我說
something
某物
yeah if you want me to say anything
是的 如果你想讓我說什麼
i'll try and read through the donations
我會嘗試通讀捐款
and if you have any requests
如果您有任何要求
for me to uh
對我來說
for me to say
讓我說
can you hear my keyboard too like
你能聽到我的鍵盤也喜歡嗎
wow that's
哇，那是
man oh my god also good morning
天哪，我的天也早安
everybody hope you're having a good day
每個人都希望你今天過得愉快
so far
迄今為止
i'm uh i'm
我是，我是
i honestly just woke up from a nap not
老實說，我剛從午睡中醒來，不是
too long ago so uh my voice is
很久以前所以我的聲音是
pretty nice and
很不錯，而且
lubed up
潤滑
for a lack of a better word oh yeah i
因為沒有更好的詞哦，是的，我
can i can try uh what's it
我可以試試呃這是什麼
i can try doing this
我可以嘗試這樣做
now hold on
現在堅持
um
嗯
i hope that didn't sound too weird and
我希望這聽起來不會太奇怪
i really don't know how that sounds so
我真的不知道這聽起來如何
uh
呃
hold on maybe i'll try on the other side
等一下，也許我會在另一邊試試
too
也
uh
呃
at least it doesn't taste weird no
至少味道不奇怪 不
no
不
ah god
天啊
it's it's honestly really
老實說，真的
embarrassing but
尷尬但
i'm glad you guys like it
我很高興你們喜歡它
oh i wonder what would happen if i
哦，我想知道如果我會發生什麼
moaned like
呻吟著
i don't think i'm gonna do that
我不認為我會那樣做
it's probably a little too much for uh
這對呃來說可能有點太多了
twitch so uh i'll try and you know
抽搐，所以我會嘗試，你知道
behave myself a little bit more instead
反而讓自己多表現一點
of trying to uh test the waters and
試圖測試水域和
maybe a little is okay not too much but
也許一點也可以，不過分
a little bit is fine right
一點點就好了
oh you're so cute
哦，你真可愛
what did what should i say
我該怎麼說
all right hold on i think a lot of
好吧，等一下，我想了很多
people wanted me to try saying something
人們想讓我試著說點什麼
along the lines of uh
沿著呃
uh good boy
好孩子
you're a very good boy
你是個好孩子
or a good girl
或者是個好女孩
yeah i'll try that hold on
是的，我會試著堅持下去
good girl
好女孩
who's a good girl
誰是好女孩
oh
哦
god
上帝
my i really do want to try like if i put
我真的很想試試，如果我放
my
我的
i feel like at this point you guys can
我覺得在這一點上你們可以
probably hear my heart heart rate from
可能聽到我的心率
far away till man it's like beating out
遠遠地，直到男人就像被打敗了
of my ears right now
我現在的耳朵
uh
呃
boyo thank you for the 6.91 cents
boyo 謝謝你的 6.91 美分
and then on thank you for the 6.90 as
然後感謝您的 6.90 as
well can you say something degrading
好吧，你能說些有辱人格的話嗎
hmm
唔
can i say something degrading huh what
我能說些有辱人格的話嗎？
do you want me to say that's degrading
你想讓我說這是有辱人格的嗎
you want me to call you a bad boy
你想讓我叫你壞孩子
this guy you know may call you
你認識的這個人可能會打電話給你
disgusting i don't know
噁心我不知道
i feel like
我覺得像
maybe i should say
也許我應該說
you're
你是
predictable
可預測的
you're very easy
你很容易
you're uh
你是
um
嗯
god i'm not i'm not used to degrading
上帝我不是我不習慣貶低
stuff too much so
東西太多了
you have to forgive me it's really uh uh
你必須原諒我這真的是呃呃
that's what i usually say
這就是我通常說的
oh
哦
oh i think i have an idea i think i do
哦，我想我有一個想法，我想我有
have an idea thank you for reminding me
有個主意謝謝你提醒我
hold on
堅持，稍等
oh you poor thing
哦，你這可憐的東西
you want kisses so badly huh
你好想親吻啊
oh that's good it's okay come here
哦，那很好，沒關係來這裡
easy now
現在容易
you want it that badly huh
你想要它那麼糟糕
maybe i hope that was uh good enough i
也許我希望那已經足夠好了，我
don't know
不知道
i stutter
我口吃
i should say i should say some of those
我應該說我應該說其中一些
uh was it
呃，是嗎
you owe me a say i love you in your uh
你欠我一句我愛你在你的呃
languages be sure to uh put it in chat i
語言一定要把它放在聊天中我
might try to uh i'll try my best all
可能會嘗試，呃，我會盡力而為
right
正確的
uh i think in french it's uh
呃，我認為法語是呃
[ __ ] them all right
[ __ ] 他們沒事
hold on
堅持，稍等
sorry
對不起
all right how can i forget oh
好吧，我怎麼能忘記哦
okay sure
好的，當然
oh my goodness you guys are so adorable
哦，天哪，你們太可愛了
you have no idea
你不知道
you're so adorable
你真可愛
come here
過來
um god
嗯上帝
oh who's my precious little darling
哦誰是我親愛的小寶貝
precious little darling
珍貴的小寶貝
palpate
觸診
all right
好的
i should probably try uh licking more i
我可能應該嘗試呃舔更多我
really do want to see if it's uh
真的很想看看是不是呃
it's really funny
真的很有趣
like
喜歡
i never would have imagined like
我從來沒有想過像
maybe biting like
也許像咬一樣
something like that
類似的東西
or uh just going back to regular
或者呃只是回到正常狀態
this is embarrassing you can see my you
這很尷尬，你可以看到我的你
can see my mouth open when i do that
當我這樣做時可以看到我的嘴張開
hold on
堅持，稍等
[Music]
[音樂]
okay
好的
i'm not in heat don't worry
我沒有發情別擔心
oh my god i feel like some some of you
哦，我的上帝，我覺得你們中的一些人
might have thought uh today was going to
可能以為你今天會
be a joke i mean it is april fool's day
開個玩笑，我的意思是今天是愚人節
but
但
ah
啊
i take this very seriously i don't think
我非常重視這個我不認為
i would ever joke about anything like
我會開玩笑說什麼
this
這
it'd be really cruel to do something
做某事真的很殘忍
like that and uh hope you guys are
就像那樣，希望你們是
no no it's not a it's not a joke it's
不不，這不是一個，這不是一個笑話，它是
the real deal
真正的交易
oh you want to kiss on both cheeks
哦，你想親吻雙頰
okay hold on
好的堅持住
okay honey
好的親愛的
be patient now
現在耐心等待
you really want to hear my heart be
你真的很想听到我的心
again okay i'll i'll do i'll do it uh
再次好吧，我會做的，我會做的，呃
another time hold on
再等一下
give me a second
你稍等一會兒
it's okay now you're safe with me
沒關係，現在你和我在一起很安全
don't worry about anything all right
什麼都別擔心
you're in my care now
你現在在我的照顧下
that's great
那太棒了
good boy
好孩子
good boy that's a very good boy
好男孩，這是一個非常好的男孩
good girl
好女孩
very good girl
很好的女孩
uh
呃
i should actually should read through
我實際上應該通讀
some of the donations as well now that
現在還有一些捐款
i'm at it
我在它
and now that i uh remember hold on
現在我記得等一下
uh nino thank you for the twenty dollars
呃尼諾謝謝你的二十美元
hope you're having a good day
希望你今天過得愉快
uh ryan thank you for the three dollars
呃 ryan 謝謝你的三美元
uh pancake thank you for the eleven
嗯煎餅謝謝你的十一
uh waka thank you for the 25
呃 waka 謝謝你的 25
good luck of the driving
祝你開車好運
and uh
呃
uh young thank you for the tier one
呃年輕謝謝你的第一層
solvent
溶劑
can you have an ara
你能有一個 ara
you want an ara
你想要一個阿拉
hold on
堅持，稍等
uh which year will it be let me see
呃 會是哪一年讓我看看
oh you guys are so adorable
哦，你們真可愛
you guys are so adorable
你們真可愛
ah you're doing so good don't worry
啊，你做得很好，別擔心
you're doing so good
你做得很好
forgive me i need to take a quick drink
原諒我，我需要快速喝一杯
of my my tea again
又是我的茶
i forget that's very audible too right
我忘了那太聽得見了
hold on let me try that again
等等，讓我再試一次
ugh
啊
oh my goodness
哦，我的天啊
i hope that didn't bother any of you i
我希望這沒有打擾你們中的任何人我
know some people don't like uh too many
知道有些人不喜歡呃太多
mouth noises or eating noises but
嘴巴發出聲音或吃東西的聲音，但
hopefully that was forgivable
希望這是可以原諒的
i have to apologize for that
我必須為此道歉
oh my goodness
哦，我的天啊
you can't focus uh be careful i don't
你不能集中註意力 呃小心我不
want you guys to get yourselves in any
希望你們在任何
trouble
麻煩
because i know it's uh
因為我知道這是呃
i know it's morning for some of you so
我知道對你們中的一些人來說現在是早上
be careful alright
小心點好嗎
easy now
現在容易
just take care of yourself first
先照顧好自己
and i'll be here
我會在這裡
god
上帝
i kind of went into this like uh without
我有點像沒有
much of a plan
很多計劃
you want me to growl
你要我咆哮
oh right i could do that as well right
哦，對了，我也可以這樣做
you're very right
你說的很對
how do i growl like
我怎麼咆哮
[Music]
[音樂]
ah
啊
maybe in the other ear tail hold on
也許在另一隻耳朵尾巴上堅持
okay that's enough of that
好吧，這就夠了
i hope that uh
我希望呃
made you happy my ears are so hot right
讓你開心我的耳朵很熱對吧
now tail god
現在尾神
uh that one made my my ears really
呃，那個讓我的耳朵真的
really blush you guys are so
你們真是臉紅
embarrassing man
尷尬的人
well all of you are so embarrassing
你們都好尷尬
oh you want a sloppy kiss
哦，你想要一個邋遢的吻
i uh hold on a sloppy kiss i don't know
我 呃 抱住 一個 邋遢 的 吻 我 不 知道
how to do that what
怎麼做
uh
呃
yeah
是的
how am i supposed to
我該怎麼做
try and do a sloppy kiss
試著做一個草率的吻
oh my goodness
哦，我的天啊
more wetness
更多的濕度
is my mouth wet enough for that
我的嘴夠濕了嗎
hold on
堅持，稍等
all right
好的
um
嗯
i don't know if that was good enough man
我不知道這是否足夠好人
i really wish i could hear this right
我真希望我能聽到這個權利
now it's i don't know what it sounds
現在我不知道這聽起來是什麼
like uh
像呃
but i'll i'll trust that it sounds okay
但我相信這聽起來不錯
on your guys's hand
在你們的手上
hold on
堅持，稍等
oh
哦
well
好吧
i tried i hope that was okay sloppy
我試過了，我希望沒關係，馬虎
kisses
吻
um
嗯
okay
好的
anyways hold on a second let me read
無論如何等一下讓我讀
through uh other donations
通過呃其他捐款
this is so nice after the tough day you
在你度過艱難的一天之後，這真是太好了
had at work but are you sure this is
有在工作，但你確定這是
your first time you're doing
你第一次做
so well too well this is my first time
太好太好了這是我的第一次
um yeah i got the uh microphone from a
嗯，是的，我從一個
fan
扇子
who uh gifted it actually through a
呃實際上是通過一個
throne so i've never had a microphone
王座，所以我從來沒有麥克風
like this before i guess it's more like
像這樣在我猜它更像是
i don't know
我不知道
i've been guided in the right direction
我被引導到正確的方向
some people
有些人
gave me some good advice too and uh i
也給了我一些很好的建議，嗯，我
don't know vox also gave me some good
不知道vox也給了我一些好
advice so i hope i'm i hope i'm doing a
建議所以我希望我希望我正在做
good job
好工作
am i doing a good job huh
我做得好嗎？
am i doing good
我做得好嗎
am i doing good darling
我做得好嗎親愛的
all right
好的
so thank you for the five tier one gift
所以謝謝你的五級禮物
subs
潛艇
and
和
you me thank you for the 520 bits can
你我謝謝你的520位可以
you say some pickup lines can i say some
你說一些接送線路我可以說一些
pickup lines
拿起線
hold on a second
稍等一下
didn't i say some last night as well
我昨晚不是也說了一些嗎
uh
呃
not the cheesy ones please that's all i
不是俗氣的，請這就是我的全部
know though
雖然知道
what are some actual good pickup lines
什麼是一些真正好的皮卡線
like
喜歡
your lips look so lonely
你的嘴唇看起來很孤獨
would they like to make mine oh yeah
他們願意做我的嗎？
that's really cheesy isn't it oh that
這真的很俗氣，不是嗎？
one is so cheesy hold on
一個太俗氣了
good
好的
good pick up lines
良好的接送線
i'm not the best at this by the way i'm
順便說一句，我不是最擅長的
really not
真的不
like
喜歡
i know so many people that are like
我認識很多人
naturally talented with doing this kind
天生有做這種事的天賦
of stuff uh
東西呃
let me see
讓我看看
are you from starbucks because i like
你是星巴克的，因為我喜歡
you a latte
你是拿鐵咖啡
that's so dumb
這太愚蠢了
oh that's so dumb what
哦，那太愚蠢了
okay
好的
uh rudy thank you for the thirteen
呃魯迪謝謝你的十三
dollars you're larry dying well i need
美元你拉里死得很好我需要
you didn't know that you needed this
你不知道你需要這個
today but thank you oh thank you for the
今天但是謝謝你哦謝謝你
donation and uh i'm happy to you know be
捐贈，我很高興你知道
of help to you if this is making you
如果這使您對您有幫助
feel better also hypnosis thank you for
感覺好多了也催眠謝謝你
the 10 000 bits as well welcome hope
10 000 位也歡迎希望
you're having a wonderful day so far
到目前為止，你度過了美好的一天
you want me to say dear or darling
你要我說親愛的還是親愛的
okay i can do that
好吧，我能做到
okay
好的
darling
寵兒
oh yeah what was that one line ah let me
哦是的那一行是什麼啊讓我
find it
找到它
okay darling
好的親愛的
kohani
科哈尼
uh
呃
how did it go again
怎麼又過去了
you want me to whimper
你想讓我嗚咽
oh my god i don't i haven't tried doing
哦，我的上帝，我沒有，我沒試過
that just yet
那隻是
won't bring her
不會帶她
[Music]
[音樂]
do i get closer should i get closer
我應該靠近嗎？
i try the other ear
我試試另一隻耳朵
hmm
唔
uh
呃
oh i found the line actually here it is
哦，我發現這條線實際上就在這裡
si
西
um
嗯
uh
呃
oh
哦
oh thank you for the 15 as well
哦，謝謝你的15
looking forward to this all week and
整個星期都在期待這一切
you're doing such a good job um it means
你做得很好，嗯，這意味著
a lot i'm glad i'm glad to know that i'm
很多我很高興我很高興知道我是
doing okay right now
現在還好
i was really worried about this
我真的很擔心這個
beforehand that's why maya my heart is
事先這就是為什麼瑪雅我的心是
so
所以
it's moving at a million miles per
它以每百萬英里的速度移動
second at the moment but that's not just
目前第二，但這不僅僅是
because of you guys obviously i mean you
因為你們，顯然我的意思是你們
guys always make my heart race but
伙計們總是讓我心跳加速，但是
i've never done anything like this
我從來沒有做過這樣的事
before so i hope it's uh i hope by
之前所以我希望它是呃我希望通過
meeting your uh
遇見你的呃
meeting your expectations
滿足您的期望
i'm doing my best
我正盡最大能力
can you say good puppy
你能說好小狗嗎
i can do that sure
我能做到
who's a good little puppy
誰是一隻好小狗
good puppy
好小狗
you're a good puppy
你是一隻好小狗
good puppy that's right
好小狗，這是對的
good puppy
好小狗
thank you for the five tier one gift
謝謝你的五層一級禮物
subs and uh
潛艇和呃
for the six dollars and ninety cents
六美元九十美分
you want me to read a poem
你要我讀一首詩
that sounds like a fun idea maybe
這聽起來是個有趣的主意
you want to have some ear rubbers what
你想要一些耳膠什麼
your robbers
你的強盜
i'm pretty sure you guys can hear this
我很確定你們能聽到這個
right
正確的
um
嗯
ah
啊
i don't think barking would be a very
我不認為吠叫會是一個非常
good idea right now honestly
老實說，現在的好主意
uh
呃
even though i would love to bark for you
即使我很想為你吠叫
right now don't think it would uh i
現在不認為它會呃我
don't think my
不要認為我的
i don't think my
我不認為我的
microphone is quite prepared to receive
麥克風已準備好接收
many parks
許多公園
you want to hear me meow
你想听我喵喵叫
yeah
是的
i don't think i can do that
我不認為我能做到
i don't know if the ear budding sounds
不知道耳塞有沒有聲音
good i really want to listen to that
很好，我真的很想听
afterwards and see if it sounds nice
之後看看它是否聽起來不錯
too much ear biting i don't know
太多的耳朵咬我不知道
ah
啊
it's a lot of ear biting right
很多人都在咬耳朵
thank you for the stream it's making my
謝謝你讓我的直播
evening no problem
晚上沒問題
good job tonight shout fall and uh yeah
今晚幹得好大喊大叫，嗯，是的
good job
好工作
i'm saluting to the mods right now as
我現在向模組致敬
well thank you for the twenty dollars
謝謝你的二十美元
oh
哦
you only need a purr i don't think i can
你只需要一個咕嚕聲我不認為我可以
purr i've tried to do it sometime but uh
咕嚕我曾經嘗試過，但是呃
it's really
是真的
really not my strong suit
真的不是我的強項
the best i can do is a little
我能做的就是一點點
but it doesn't really sound like a bird
但它聽起來不像是一隻鳥
does it
可以
you want me to call you a good little
你要我叫你好小
kid
孩子
okay
好的
uh hold on
呃等等
oh who's a good little kitten
哦，誰是一隻好小貓
that's right you are
沒錯，你是
good kitten
好小貓
[Applause]
[掌聲]
i honestly forgot about the sound alerts
老實說，我忘記了聲音警報
that scared me for a second
嚇了我一秒
i'm gonna have to turn that off for the
我得把它關掉
stream sorry
流抱歉
i completely forgot about that
我完全忘記了
ah goodkin who's my good little kitten
啊古德金誰是我的好小貓
you are
你是
you're mine
你是我的
all
全部
right i'm not satisfied um
對，我不滿意嗯
you don't have an asmr prompts but you
你沒有 asmr 提示，但你
just wanted to support thank you for the
只是想支持謝謝你
streams they're really calming while you
當你流著它們真的很平靜
work nox said thank you for the 10 and
工作 nox 說謝謝你的 10 和
98 cents
98 美分
you want some ear scratches delia uh can
你想要一些耳朵抓痕迪莉婭呃可以
i do that let me
我這樣做讓我
i don't know
我不知道
it really just sounds like
聽起來真的很像
let me touch rubbing the rubbing the ear
讓我摸摸摸摸耳朵
at this point i don't think i can i
在這一點上，我認為我不能
don't think i have the materials too but
不要以為我也沒有材料，但是
uh maybe next time
呃，也許下次
you want me to say mommy
你要我說媽媽
sure i can do that as well
當然我也可以
i don't know if i should do it in the
我不知道我是否應該在
lower or higher tone but i'll do i'll
更低或更高的音調，但我會的，我會的
try a few different ones alright just
試試幾個不同的就好了
for you
為你
mommy
媽媽
all right
好的
oh yeah i have to do daddy as well right
哦，是的，我也必須做爸爸，對吧
because uh
因為呃
ah daddy
啊爸爸
daddy
爸爸
it feels loud oh god i'm so embarrassed
感覺很吵哦，天哪，我好尷尬
man it's so embarrassing
男人太尷尬了
you're doing great you've been excited
你做得很好你很興奮
for this all week can you try the
這整個星期你能試試嗎
pufferfish sound it always gives you the
河豚的聲音它總是給你
asmr if i just want to do it the
asmr 如果我只想這樣做
pufferfish sound that's a very odd
河豚的聲音很奇怪
request to do but uh sure i can give it
請求做，但你確定我可以給它
a try as well hold on
嘗試以及堅持
what
什麼
[ __ ] puffer fish right
[ __ ] 河豚魚對
oh my goodness that's funny
哦，天哪，這很有趣
good request
好要求
a very funny request
一個非常有趣的要求
uh
呃
captain thank you for the ten dollars
船長謝謝你的十美元
and uh let me see
呃讓我看看
sayo thank you for the two dollars as
說謝謝你的兩美元
well
好吧
and minty thank you for the 10. can you
和薄荷謝謝你的10。你能
do some popping noises they sound really
發出一些爆裂聲，它們聽起來真的
cool popping noises as well
還有很酷的爆裂聲
popping
彈出
with my mouth like mouth pops
用我的嘴巴像嘴巴一樣
sounds cute yeah
聽起來很可愛是的
you guys can really hear my mouth you
你們真的能聽到我的嘴
know with this microphone i don't know
知道這個麥克風我不知道
about that
關於那個
oh you want more kisses huh
哦，你想要更多的吻，呵呵
you want more kisses so bad
你想要更多的吻太糟糕了
maybe if you beg for it oh god i can't
也許如果你乞求它哦上帝我不能
do that
去做
oh
哦
it's so embarrassing man it's so [ __ ]
這太令人尷尬了，這太[__]
embarrassing but
尷尬但
how about you say please
你說好嗎
all right how about you say please maybe
好吧，你說好嗎？
i'll consider
我會考慮
okay
好的
good girl
好女孩
who's a good girl
誰是好女孩
uh
呃
can you say you'll see you'll see
你能說你會看到嗎？
that's really cool it means like good
這真的很酷 這意味著很好
boy when you're stroking your lovers or
男孩，當你撫摸你的愛人或
a kid's head
一個孩子的頭
sure i can try
我當然可以試試
that's right
這是正確的
who's a good boy
誰是好孩子
you worked really hard today
你今天真的很努力
good job
好工作
i'm proud of you
我以你為榮
i'm so proud of you
我很為你驕傲
good boy
好孩子
very good boys
非常好的男孩
uh
呃
you want to hear the heartbeat again one
你想再聽一次心跳
more time
更多時間
heartbeat
心跳
okay i'll do it another time since you
好吧，我會再做一次，因為你
guys like it a lot
伙計們非常喜歡它
uh
呃
i hope that satisfied you
我希望你滿意
some dirty talks
一些骯髒的談話
oh don't worry we've already done plenty
哦別擔心我們已經做了很多
of that i don't think that's any prob
我認為這沒有任何問題
any problem
任何問題
why can we hear that because uh if i get
為什麼我們能聽到，因為呃，如果我得到
a little closer
更近一點
and uh press my chest against my
然後把我的胸部壓在我的
microphone you guys should be able to
麥克風你們應該可以
you guys should be able to hear it
你們應該能聽到
yeah it does beat fast i'm kind of
是的，它確實跳得很快，我有點
you guys do make me
你們確實讓我
flustered sometimes i guess but
我想有時會心慌，但是
yeah
是的
yeah just leaning towards the microphone
是的，只是靠在麥克風上
um
嗯
alay thank you for the donation can you
謝謝你的捐贈，你能
say good bunny please you're doing so
說好兔子請你這樣做
good
好的
um
嗯
hold on give me a second
稍等一下
good bunny
好兔子
all right
好的
ah
啊
god why is that embarrassing
上帝為什麼這麼尷尬
good bunny
好兔子
who's a good bunny
誰是好兔子
very good bunny
非常好的兔子
okay sure i can try and do that
好的，我可以嘗試這樣做
just for you
只為你
uh
呃
um
嗯
oh wait was the one in uh russian i
哦，等等，是那個俄語的我
remember it
記住它
i think i remember how to do it in
我想我記得怎麼做
russian as well
俄語也是
uh what else
呃還有什麼
oh of course
哦，當然
maharakita
萬原北
darling
寵兒
i love saying uh i love adding miyamor
我喜歡說，嗯，我喜歡添加 miyamor
and me vida at the end of uh
和我維達在呃結束時
all those kinds of
所有這些
uh
呃
everything like that but
像這樣的一切，但
it's really it's really nice to add a
真的很高興添加一個
little bit more of a uh you know a
多一點你知道的
little tease at the end of it like
在它的結尾有點挑逗喜歡
so i love spanish sometimes it's really
所以我喜歡西班牙語有時真的
cute
可愛的
uh
呃
in korean too i think i already did that
在韓語中，我想我已經這樣做了
but i can do it again sure right
但我可以再做一次
um
嗯
is
是
uh gerard thank you for the 6.90 sir
呃杰拉德謝謝你的6.90先生
this is a wendy's
這是溫迪的
uh would you like the number nine with
呃，你想要九號嗎？
your combo meal i recommend that and uh
我推薦你的套餐，嗯
maybe a side of medium fries
也許是中薯條的一面
asmr pov i take you on a date to uh the
asmr pov 我帶你去約會
wendy's drive-through
溫迪的得來速
parentheses you don't have enough money
括號你沒有足夠的錢
i don't know i love those uh funny
我不知道我喜歡那些有趣的
little uh you know how i can asmrs they
呃，你知道我怎麼能asmrs他們
have those uh
有那些呃
little
小的
explanations on the side one of my
我的一側的解釋
favorites was uh when there was this
收藏夾是呃當有這個的時候
like
喜歡
uh pov it's the 1800s and
呃 pov 這是 1800 年代和
you
你
you're bedridden and i'm taking care of
你臥床不起，我來照顧
you and then it's like in parentheses
你然後就像在括號裡
you have the plague
你有瘟疫
that's so funny
那太有趣了
i love those so much or a pov i beat the
我非常喜歡那些或我擊敗的 pov
[ __ ] of you until you fall asleep
[ __ ] 你們直到入睡
asmr to help you sleep i beat you until
asmr 幫助你入睡我打敗你直到
you're unconscious right that's all it
你是無意識的 對 僅此而已
is
是
i love the contacts it's adorable
我喜歡那些可愛的聯繫人
all right
好的
uh jasmine thank you for the donation
呃茉莉謝謝你的捐贈
you say good job sure i can i can do
你說乾得好，我當然可以，我可以
that
那
i don't know if i can add the
我不知道我是否可以添加
ah maybe i can
啊，也許我可以
good job you dirty girl
幹得好你這個骯髒的女孩
good job
好工作
uh you want me to say
呃你想讓我說
lao
老
that means husband ah i don't know what
這意味著丈夫啊我不知道是什麼
it means husband that's kiel
這意味著丈夫是基爾
kong
港
all right
好的
all right remember i think someone
好吧，記得我想有人
taught me that it said uh
教我它說呃
it's another term of endearment
這是另一個愛稱
no
不
uh what else to do what else can we do
呃還能做什麼我們還能做什麼
how else to make you
還有什麼能讓你
even more flustered
更慌張
kiss me [ __ ] get over here
吻我[__]到這裡來
be more demanding yeah
要求更高是的
get over here right now
馬上過來
ah all right
啊好吧
oh sorry about that that was my uh
哦對不起那是我的呃
that's my coaster
那是我的過山車
sure i can do that
我當然可以
you're so cute
你真可愛
oh you guys are so cute
哦，你們真可愛
more typing
更多打字
oh you guys like the typing huh
哦，你們喜歡打字哈
sure i can do a little bit of that as
當然我可以做一點
well
好吧
you would think i wrote uh something
你會認為我寫了一些東西
that was comprehensible in that but i
這是可以理解的，但我
just typed up a bunch of gibberish and
剛打了一堆亂碼
uh see nobody would even know
呃，看沒人會知道
nobody would even know
甚至沒有人會知道
uh
呃
alexis thank you for the uh oh
亞歷克西斯謝謝你哦哦
forty dollars and five cents
四十美元五美分
uh you're watching while driving home
呃，你開車回家的時候在看
i'll be careful please don't uh watch
我會小心的請不要看
while you drive okay
當你開車沒事的時候
take care
小心
of yourself and uh watch keep your eyes
你自己和呃注意保持你的眼睛
on the road
在路上
i don't know what i would do if uh any
我不知道如果有的話我會怎麼做
of you guilty's got yourselves hurt so
你們有罪的讓自己受傷了
please take care of yourselves and uh
請照顧好自己，呃
don't
別
don't put yourselves in any danger for
不要將自己置於任何危險之中
my sake alright and i worry about you
看在我的份上，我很擔心你
guys a lot and i care about you a lot so
伙計們很多，我很關心你，所以
don't uh
不要哦
don't do anything stupid
不要做任何愚蠢的事
all right silly
好吧 傻
be safe
注意安全
uh
呃
you want me to do a girly moan
你要我做一個少女的呻吟
a girly moan what
少女的呻吟是什麼
uh maybe i can try
呃，也許我可以試試
[Laughter]
[笑聲]
all right all right that's the most i
好吧好吧那是我最
can do probably no not too much not too
可以做 大概 不 不太多 不太多
much not too much
不多不少
um
嗯
oh man you might have my heart bro my
哦，伙計，你可能有我的心，我的兄弟
heart yeah bye oh very bye very good bye
心 是 再見 哦 非常 再見 非常 再見
uh seth ross thank you for the fifty
呃塞思羅斯謝謝你的五十
dollars hope you're having a great time
美元希望你玩得開心
so far as well and
到目前為止
thank you for the uh donation you're
謝謝你的捐贈
really hungry before this and that
在這之前真的很餓
you're not anymore
你已經不在了
i hope that's a good thing
我希望這是件好事
you're really good at this is it
你真的很擅長這個
possible to have a mukbang in the future
未來可能有吃播
look what i have hold on
看看我堅持了什麼
let's see how this sounds
讓我們看看這聽起來如何
i was prepared for something like this
我已經為這樣的事情做好了準備
what was i crunching on uh there's
我在忙什麼，呃有
nothing much just some pretzels all i
沒什麼，只是一些椒鹽脆餅而已
wanted to do was just uh make sure i had
想做的只是確保我有
a bag of something on the stem by voila
莖上的一袋東西，瞧
because i thought it'd be kind of nice
因為我覺得會很好
to see uh how that would sound
看看呃聽起來怎麼樣
it's very crunchy i feel like crunches
它非常脆，我感覺像脆脆的
are some of the best uh
是一些最好的呃
asmr sounds
asmr 聲音
i don't know if i'll ever do a mukbang
我不知道我是否會做吃播
in the future but uh i do like
在未來，但我確實喜歡
i don't know maybe i can consider it who
我不知道也許我可以考慮誰
knows
知道
not sure anyone would listen to that
不確定有人會聽嗎
really uh
真的呃
can you be called goshichen sama
你可以叫goshichen sama嗎
goshijin sama
後人大人
kosujinsama
甲須人間
doesn't that mean master
那不就是主人的意思嗎
now doesn't that mean master or
現在這不意味著主人或
something hold
東西持有
on let me blow
讓我吹
i feel like that might be too loud
我覺得那可能太大聲了
you're such a good boy
你真是個好孩子
good boy good boy
好孩子好孩子
you're doing so good
你做得很好
who's a good boy
誰是好孩子
hold on
堅持，稍等
you're such a good girl
你真是個好女孩
good girl
好女孩
you're a very good girl
你是個好女孩
you're doing so good
你做得很好
very good
很好
good girl
好女孩
i feel like i can't say that one though
我覺得我不能這麼說
because it's like isn't that only
因為它不僅如此
exclusive to howl
嚎叫專用
nah okay fine i
不，好吧，我
that's my girl
這才是我的姑娘
i don't think i can ever uh stand up to
我不認為我可以忍受
his you know
他你知道的
to his level but
到他的水平，但
uh
呃
zach thank you for the uh donation and
扎克謝謝你的捐贈和
uh alexandra thank you for the 69 what a
呃，亞歷山德拉，謝謝你的 69
very auspicious number
非常吉祥的數字
can you get an omni oh since so many of
你能得到一個全方位的哦，因為這麼多
you guys asked nicely yes i can
你們問得很好，是的，我可以
on the time
準時
on eton
在伊頓
maybe i should do it in a higher voice
也許我應該用更高的聲音做
god
上帝
okay that's the only time i will ever do
好吧，這是我唯一一次做
it
它
you guys get it that just just the once
你們明白了，這只是一次
and that's it never again never again
這就是它再也不會再
ah
啊
chloe thank you for the bits
克洛伊謝謝你的位
you may say sure i can do that as well
你可能會說我也能做到
you're mine
你是我的
[Music]
[音樂]
you've been a very good boy
你是個好孩子
you're mine
你是我的
you've been a very good girl
你是個好女孩
uh wong thank you for the uh eleven
嗯，王謝謝你，嗯，十一
dollars
美元
you'd love to hear me say i love you
你很想听我說我愛你
says in chinese
用中文說
uh
呃
i can try sure i hope it i hope this is
我可以嘗試確定我希望它我希望這是
the right translation it's not anything
正確的翻譯不是什麼
saucy but
俏皮但是
uh
呃
thank you for the 15
謝謝你的15
okay all right
好吧好吧
hey mama
嘿媽媽
was it hey lil mama hey little mama
是不是嘿小媽媽嘿小媽媽
foxy mama hey mama
狡猾的媽媽嘿媽媽
she's a cool thank you for the 13
她很酷，謝謝你的 13
well i
好吧，我
need
需要
oh man it's really
哦，伙計，真的
it's really i love how how cute
我真的很喜歡多麼可愛
saying i love you in chinese sounds
用中文說我愛你
that mean good boy in the spanish i
這意味著西班牙語中的好男孩我
think
思考
sure
當然
you want to hear me giggle a little bit
你想听我咯咯笑
more oh don't worry i think
更多哦，別擔心，我想
you'll have
你會有
you'll have plenty of that
你會有很多
as we uh as we go along tonight
當我們今晚一起去的時候
you want me to call all the good boys in
你想讓我把所有的好孩子都叫進來
the chat handsome
聊天帥
for all my boys listening out there
對於我所有在外面聽的男孩
you're very handsome
你很帥
very very handsome
非常非常帥
good boy
好孩子
who's a good boy
誰是好孩子
who's a good boy no
誰是好孩子不
he's a good boy
他是個好孩子
and uh oh thank you for the three
哦，謝謝你的三個
dollars and thirty three cents uh potter
美元和三十三美分呃波特
thank you for the donation you want me
謝謝你想要我的捐贈
to bowl you into doing your work
讓你做你的工作
hey now
嘿現在
what are you doing
你在做什麼
what are you just sitting around for huh
你只是為了什麼而坐在那裡
how about you get your ass up and
你要不要站起來
start being responsible
開始負責
i'll still make you
我還是會讓你
i'm sorry i can't take it
對不起，我不能接受
sometimes it's hard but oh god how do
有時很難，但天哪，怎麼辦
people how do people be so dominant in
人們怎麼會如此占主導地位
these types of situations i got my ears
這些類型的情況我得到了我的耳朵
you better get up into your work if you
你最好開始你的工作，如果你
know what's good for you you [ __ ]
知道什麼對你有好處[ __ ]
dirty girl
骯髒的女孩
okay
好的
uh gunday for the donation asmr blv
呃，為捐贈 asmr blv 準備的槍戰
we're on a date at costco but they're
我們在costco約會，但他們是
out of hot dogs and you're really upset
沒有熱狗，你真的很沮喪
but then they say that i can have your
但後來他們說我可以擁有你的
hot dog instead wow all right well
熱狗，而不是哇很好
uh biba thank you for the ten dollars
呃 biba 謝謝你的十美元
this is the best shopper he got
這是他得到的最好的購物者
goosebumps
雞皮疙瘩
i'm glad i'm glad it's uh it's sounding
我很高興我很高興這是呃它聽起來
a lot better it's honestly i have no
好多了，老實說我沒有
idea it was going to be it's going to be
想它會是它會是
this
這
sound so good on your guys i really do
聽起來對你們來說太好了，我真的很喜歡
have to make sure if i can
必須確定我是否可以
see if it sounds
看看它是否聽起來
as good as you say it does
和你說的一樣好
i'll check out the vod afterwards but
之後我會查看視頻，但是
you're really sweet thank you
你真的很可愛謝謝你
i love you
我愛你
uh you want me to do some humming
呃你想讓我哼唱
humming
哼唱
what kind of song maybe close to you
什麼樣的歌可能離你很近
hey
嘿
[Music]
[音樂]
me
我
uh
呃
i hope you like that
我希望你喜歡
don't worry you're safe with me
別擔心你和我在一起很安全
just take it easy all right
放輕鬆就好
i know you guys work really hard every
我知道你們每個人都很努力
day and uh
天和呃
you can just take a moment and
你可以花點時間
make sure you rest with me
確保你和我一起休息
good job today very good job today i'm
今天干得好今天干得好我是
so proud of you
為你驕傲
very very proud of you
非常非常為你感到驕傲
good job
好工作
[Music]
[音樂]
that's it
而已
that's right
這是正確的
good
好的
you're doing very good
你做得很好
your laughter is the best sound of all
你的笑聲是最好的聲音
uh story thank you for the donation
呃故事謝謝你的捐贈
i'm glad you guys like how i sound when
我很高興你們喜歡我的聲音
i laugh it means a lot um
我笑了，這意味著很多
thank you for all that you do shawtal
謝謝你所做的一切
thank you for coming by and uh show me a
謝謝你的光臨，你給我看一個
good time
美好時光
uh you want me to say
呃你想讓我說
vox and mista in the sexiest way
最性感的vox和mista
possible
可能的
thank you for the tonation but uh
謝謝你的語調，但是呃
i think i can do that
我想我能做到
i mean sure why not
我的意思是肯定為什麼不
i i feel like this is going to be used
ii 感覺這個會被使用
against me in some way but uh
以某種方式反對我，但是呃
okay
好的
mr
先生
vox
聲音
oh fox
哦狐狸
a vox
一個聲音
vox
聲音
okay
好的
just because you had such a generous
就因為你有這麼大方
donation i appreciate it uh
捐贈我很感激
normally i don't think i would do that
通常我不認為我會那樣做
but uh just this once
但是，就這一次
uh tanya thank you for the donation to
呃 tanya 謝謝你的捐贈
can you say something to wake me up or
你能說點什麼來叫醒我嗎？
to go to bed
去睡覺
sure i can i can do that
我當然可以 我能做到
oh
哦
good morning darling
早上好親愛的
did you sleep well
你睡的好嗎
you're gonna do great today okay
你今天會做得很好的
make sure you remember to
確保你記得
take your medicine
吃藥
i care about you a lot okay
我很關心你好嗎
have a good day baby
有一個美好的一天寶貝
take care
小心
i love you
我愛你
i hope that was uh that suffices for a
我希望這足以滿足
good morning
早上好
uh
呃
you thank you for the 520
謝謝你的520
say something to
說些什麼
go to bed
睡覺
hmm i feel like i said something before
嗯我覺得我之前說過什麼
already in
已經在
the same lines but uh
相同的台詞，但是呃
sure
當然
you work so hard today
你今天很努力
please rest all you want all right
請好好休息
take care of yourself
照顧好你自己
i'll protect you don't worry
我會保護你別擔心
you work so hard
你工作這麼努力
you're doing such a good job too babe
你也做得很好，寶貝
i love you
我愛你
sleep well okay
睡個好覺
uh good morning uh honey thank you for
嗯，早上好，親愛的，謝謝你
the donation as well
捐贈也是
good boy good boy
好孩子好孩子
good boy
好孩子
[Music]
[音樂]
who's a good boy who's a good boy
誰是好孩子 誰是好孩子
who's a good boy
誰是好孩子
all right
好的
don't have a request i just want to tell
沒有要求我只想告訴
you're doing a great job oh god
你做得很好哦上帝
i'm glad you guys are enjoying it a lot
我很高興你們玩得很開心
so far
迄今為止
again it made me really nervous to try
再次嘗試讓我很緊張
this out but it's nice to see that
這齣來了，但很高興看到
everyone is approving of uh
每個人都讚成呃
approving of my efforts so far
批准我迄今為止的努力
um
嗯
can you please say in japanese
你能用日語說嗎
[Music]
[音樂]
how did that one line go
那一行是怎麼走的
hmm
唔
can you tell us it's going to be okay
你能告訴我們一切都會好的嗎
of course honey
當然親愛的
everything is going to be okay
所有事情都會好起來的
you don't have anything to worry about
你不用擔心
now
現在
i got you
我接到你了
all right
好的
everything's going to be okay
一切都會好起來的
uh
呃
okay thank you for the donation nico
好的謝謝你的捐贈nico
thank you for the donation as well and
也感謝您的捐贈
uh amber thank you for the donation
嗯琥珀謝謝你的捐贈
can you say something like you better go
你能說像你這樣的話最好走嗎
to sleep soon good nights have a sweet
早點睡覺 晚安 有一個甜蜜
dream
夢
i can
我能
i can try
我可以試試
honey you better go to sleep soon okay
親愛的，你最好快點睡覺，好嗎？
good night
晚安
and have a sweet dream okay
做個美夢好嗎
well i need
我需要
you better sleep soon you idiot
你最好早點睡，你這個白痴
please sleep soon all right
請快點睡好
don't make me worry
別讓我擔心
you're so silly
你真傻
you are so silly
你真是太傻了
okay
好的
oh man i'm running low on t right now
哦，伙計，我現在沒錢了
wow
哇
running very low on t
在 t 上運行非常低
it's already been almost an hour oh it
已經快一個小時了哦
already has been an hour how time flies
已經一個小時了 時間過得真快
when we were just uh messing around and
當我們只是在胡鬧的時候
uh
呃
licking some mirrors
舔一些鏡子
you hope uh fox is missing no i'm sorry
你希望呃狐狸不見了，對不起
i had to earned every penny
我必須賺到每一分錢
thank you for the donation again it's
再次感謝您的捐贈
very much appreciated
非常感謝
uh
呃
say good morning balbay
說早安巴爾貝
sure
當然
good morning
早上好
i don't know how that's i really need to
我不知道那是我真正需要的
listen to how the ear bites sound i'm
聽聽耳朵咬我的聲音
gonna try biting ears okay how's this uh
會試著咬耳朵好嗎？
yeah let me know how the uh your biting
是的，讓我知道你是怎麼咬人的
would go
會去
um
嗯
yes indeed i did lick it it had very
是的，我確實舔過它
much did lick it
舔了很多
uh
呃
um
嗯
nova thank you for the donation can you
新星謝謝你的捐贈，你能
scold us pretty please
請漂亮地罵我們
scolding you say uh sure i don't know
罵你說我確定我不知道
you need probably need a line
你可能需要一條線
scolding
罵
lines
線條
off
離開
sure
當然
i i don't know
我不知道
uh
呃
i don't
我不
i'm looking at oh don't don't look at me
我在看哦，別看我
i don't know how to i don't know how to
我不知道怎麼做 我不知道怎麼做
to scold
罵
people
人們
there's only one weird way that i can
我只有一種奇怪的方法
i don't know if it's a good idea oh wait
我不知道這是不是個好主意哦等等
i could uh i think i know
我可以，呃，我想我知道
huh
呵呵
you want a kiss from me
你想給我一個吻
don't be a [ __ ] idiot
不要做一個 [ __ ] 白痴
why would i want to kiss you
我為什麼要吻你
can you even reach me you're not even
你能聯繫到我嗎？
five feet tall
五英尺高
shorty
矮個子
yes i did just call of you short
是的，我只是簡短地打電話給你
i
一世
i fully i fully believe that uh yeah
我完全相信，嗯，是的
i'm not uh i'm not as short as you guys
我不是呃我沒有你們那麼矮
make me out to be i think some of you
讓我成為我想你們中的一些人
guys are just projecting
伙計們只是在投射
i'm not short
我不矮
i'm not sure
我不知道
you guys are just mean
你們只是卑鄙
uh ciao thank you for the ten dollars
呃 ciao 謝謝你的十美元
good morning
早上好
and uh alex thank you for the donation
呃，亞歷克斯謝謝你的捐贈
can you say
你可以說
oh
哦
yeah maybe i can
是的，也許我可以
i bet you won't call
我打賭你不會打電話
oh
哦
hold on
堅持，稍等
i bet you won't be calling me a bottom
我敢打賭你不會叫我屁股
by the end of the night
到深夜
is that bottom to you huh
那是你的底線嗎？
dumb ass
笨蛋
uh oh
哦哦
thank you for the 10 000 bits hope
感謝您的 10 000 位希望
you're having a good morning or a good
你早上好
evening i'll come
晚上我會來
and uh um thank you for the uh sub
嗯嗯謝謝你的子
welcome to the guild
歡迎加入公會
all right
好的
now
現在
what else can we do
我們還能做什麼
i've always said that line though
不過我一直都這麼說
haven't i i feel like i have already
我不覺得我已經
that's my girl
這才是我的姑娘
that's my boy
這是我的男孩
good boy
好孩子
very good boy
很好的男孩
who's a good boy
誰是好孩子
that's my boy
這是我的男孩
good girl
好女孩
that's my girl
這才是我的姑娘
who's a good girl
誰是好女孩
good girl
好女孩
very good girl
很好的女孩
[Laughter]
[笑聲]
uh
呃
yeah i tried don't think i can hold a
是的，我試過了，我認為我不能持有
candle to hell but again i try
蠟燭地獄，但我再次嘗試
try my best
盡我全力
okay
好的
sorry
對不起
just had to do a quick stretch real fast
只需要真正快速地做一個快速伸展
uh oh my goodness uh frost thank you so
哦，天哪，呃，霜，謝謝你
much for the
非常適合
big donation very big donation oh my god
大捐贈 非常大的捐贈 哦，我的上帝
your day was [ __ ] until now and you just
到目前為止，你的日子是 [ __ ]，而你只是
made it a lot better thank you for being
讓它變得更好謝謝你
who you are
你是誰
i'm glad you're enjoying the uh the not
我很高興你在享受 uh the not
so say so asmr but
所以這麼說 asmr 但是
i hope you're i did make your day
我希望你是我讓你開心的一天
that much better
好多了
really
真的
i'm sorry it was uh very bad but uh
我很抱歉這是呃非常糟糕但是呃
hopefully now you can relax and
希望現在你可以放鬆
take uh
拿呃
take some time to just
花點時間
de-stress and relax now that you're with
和你一起減壓和放鬆
us
我們
you may say yes my oh hold on can i
你可能會說是的，我的哦，等等，我可以嗎？
yes
是的
my lord
我的主
sebastian style
塞巴斯蒂安風格
yes my lord
是的我的主
i don't know if i can he's uh he's a
我不知道我能不能他是呃他是
very he's very [ __ ] uh
非常他非常[__]呃
you know
你懂的
that guy is very
那傢伙很
um
嗯
sebastian's very uh i don't know
塞巴斯蒂安很好，我不知道
i don't think i can ever achieve his
我不認為我能達到他的目標
amount of uh you know dominantness
嗯，你知道占主導地位的數量
of course my love
當然是我的愛
yeah i can do that
是的，我能做到
yes dear yes my love
是的，親愛的，是的，我的愛
yes darling
是，親愛的
of course darling
當然親愛的
now
現在
now what else to do let's see
現在還能做什麼讓我們看看
oh yeah that's right baby
哦，是的，這是正確的寶貝
that's right
這是正確的
okay
好的
uh
呃
i've already done um i've already said i
我已經完成了，我已經說過了
love you in a few different languages
用幾種不同的語言愛你
already so
已經如此
sucking noises
吸吮的聲音
sucking noises wait how do i do sucking
吸吮的聲音等我怎麼吸
noises
噪音
can you please say i love you in french
你能用法語說我愛你嗎
okay you want me to read a poem what
好吧你要我讀一首詩什麼
kind of poem should i read then i don't
我應該讀什麼樣的詩然後我不讀
know
知道
reading a poem sucking on my fingers can
讀一首吮吸手指的詩可以
i do that hold on
我堅持
hmm i guess i can wow
嗯，我想我可以哇
who would have thought wow all right i
誰會想到哇，好吧，我
don't know how loud that was oh god i've
不知道那聲音有多響，我的天啊
never oh okay well
從來沒有哦，好吧
i hope that didn't sound too uh too
我希望那聽起來也不太好
uh
呃
guys
伙計們
stop embarrassing me
別讓我難堪了
uh
呃
love poems
情詩
some love poems huh
一些情詩吧
all right
好的
ah
啊
let's see what is a good love poem
讓我們看看什麼是好的情詩
one million stars
一百萬顆星星
up in the sky
在天際之上
one shines brighter and i can't deny
一個更亮，我不能否認
hello so precious
你好如此珍貴
i love so true
我愛得如此真實
a love that comes from me to you
從我到你的愛
wow that was cheesy as [ __ ]
哇，這太俗氣了[__]
that was cheesy as hell
那太俗氣了
but it was still cute still pretty damn
但它仍然很可愛
cute
可愛的
oh my god all of these poems look so
哦，我的上帝，所有這些詩看起來都如此
i love that comes alright i love how you
我喜歡那來的好我喜歡你
uh
呃
you know you want to fix it on that sing
你知道你想修復那首歌
the other part but okay
另一部分，但還可以
i don't know any good poems though
雖然我不知道有什麼好詩
i don't know if anybody has some uh some
我不知道是否有人有一些呃一些
good poem recommendations but okay
好詩推薦，但還可以
can you make a ringtone like
你能做一個像這樣的鈴聲嗎
you have a call
你有電話
okay
好的
a spicy poem yeah that's the thing i
一首辛辣的詩是的，我就是這樣
don't know i don't know any uh spicy
不知道我不知道任何呃辣
poems so
詩如此
um
嗯
[Music]
[音樂]
okay
好的
uh what can i hold you with it's a
呃，我能用它來抱你嗎？
really gentle one
真的很溫柔
what can
什麼可以
i hold you with
我抱著你
poem
詩
oh this one doesn't seem to yeah sure i
哦，這個似乎不太確定我
can try
可以嘗試
what can i hold you with
我能拿什麼抱你
i offer you lean streets desperate
我為你提供絕望的街道
sunsets
日落
the moon of the jagged suburbs i offer
我提供的鋸齒狀郊區的月亮
you the bitterness of a man who has
你是一個男人的苦澀
looked long and long at the lonely moon
久久地望著孤單的月亮
i offer you my ancestors my dead men the
我給你我的祖先我的死人
ghosts that living men have honored in
活人所尊敬的鬼魂
bronze my father's father killed in the
青銅 我父親的父親在
frontier of bruno's eras
布魯諾時代的前沿
two bullets through his lung
兩顆子彈穿過他的肺
bearded and dead
大鬍子死了
wrapped by his soldiers what the heck
被他的士兵包裹著
wait
等待
what is this
這是什麼
it's gentle
很溫柔
i thought you said it's gentle either
我以為你說它也很溫柔
this seems very uh
這看起來很呃
maybe this is the wrong one
也許這是錯誤的
is this the is this the right one that
這是不是這個是正確的那個
got really dark
真的很黑
[Laughter]
[笑聲]
oh was that the right one
哦，那是對的嗎
ah
啊
[Music]
[音樂]
oh hold on maybe it's this one hold on i
哦，等等，也許是這個，等等我
think i might have just picked the wrong
想我可能選錯了
one here we go
我們去
uh what can i hold you with
呃，我能拿什麼抱你
i offer you lean streets desperate
我為你提供絕望的街道
sunsets the moon over the ragged suburbs
在破爛的郊區落下月亮
i offer you the bitterness of a man who
我給你一個男人的苦澀
has looked long and long at the lonely
久久地註視著寂寞
moon
月亮
i offer you explanations of yourself
我向你解釋你自己
theories about yourself
關於你自己的理論
authentic and surprising news of
真實而令人驚訝的消息
yourself
你自己
i can give you my loneliness my darkness
我可以給你我的寂寞我的黑暗
the hunger of my heart i'm trying to
我內心的飢餓，我正在努力
bribe you of uncertainty with danger
用危險賄賂你的不確定性
with defeat
失敗
okay so that's the same poem well
好吧，那是同一首詩
the the entire in between is quite dark
中間的整體很暗
as well but you know thank you for the
以及，但你知道謝謝你
recommendation
推薦
that was a joke
那隻是個玩笑
was that a joke i don't know
我不知道那是個玩笑嗎
uh amber thank you for the donation as
嗯琥珀謝謝你的捐贈
well uh you've been having a hard time
嗯，你一直很難過
on your study recently can you say
你最近的學習能不能說
something to push you to do more
促使你做更多的事情
uh
呃
to encourage you to study
鼓勵你學習
sure
當然
thank you for the donation as well
也感謝您的捐贈
oh you guys are making me flustered now
哦，你們現在讓我心慌
why is everyone making me so flustered
為什麼大家都讓我這麼慌張
now
現在
god how did this happen huh how the hell
上帝這是怎麼發生的
did this happen
這發生過嗎
okay
好的
i'm using a lullaby i don't think uh
我在用搖籃曲我不認為呃
this uh microphone would be very good
這個呃麥克風會很好
for uh for singing but
呃 唱歌 但是
you know i uh
你知道我呃
i might i don't know i'll try another
我可能不知道我會嘗試另一個
time if i can if i know how
如果我可以的話，如果我知道怎麼做的話
the microphone sounds uh with singing in
麥克風在唱歌
the future i can try another time in the
未來我可以再試一次
future right
未來權利
you want me to do
你要我做
what is that the raven is a good one
烏鴉是什麼好烏鴉
the raven is a good poem you said okay
烏鴉是一首好詩你說好的
it's by oh it's the one by edgar allan
哦，這是埃德加·艾倫的那個
poe
坡
this is a really long poem
這是一首很長的詩
hold on
堅持，稍等
i mean maybe i can try doing that as
我的意思是也許我可以嘗試這樣做
well right
好吧
funny enough
夠有趣的
i've never read the raven song
我從未讀過烏鴉之歌
oh you want more kisses
哦，你想要更多的吻
i'm sorry i haven't been giving you
對不起，我沒有給你
enough attention have i
我有足夠的注意力
hmm
唔
there you go needy
你去有需要的
what a needy needy
多麼有需要的人
needy brat you are
你是個窮小子
okay
好的
the raven
烏鴉
let's see
讓我們來看看
once upon a been night dreary while i
曾幾何時，我的夜晚很沉悶
pondered weak and weary over many
對許多人感到虛弱和疲倦
acquainting curious volume of forgotten
熟悉的被遺忘的好奇卷
lore
知識
while i nodded in nearly napping
當我幾乎打盹時點點頭
suddenly there came a tapping
突然傳來敲擊聲
as of someone gently rapping rapping at
就像有人輕輕敲打
my chamber door
我的房間門
tis some visitor i muttered tapping at
是某個訪客，我低聲敲打著
my chamber door only this and nothing
我的房間門只有這個，什麼都沒有
more
更多的
ah distinctly i remember
啊，我清楚地記得
it was in the bleak december
那是在淒涼的十二月
and each separate dying ember
和每一個單獨的垂死的餘燼
wrought its ghost upon the floor
在地板上製造它的幽靈
eagerly i wish tomorrow if inly i sought
我熱切地希望明天如果我尋求
to borrow
去借
from my books
從我的書中
cersei's of sorrow
瑟曦的悲傷
sorrow for the lost lenore
為失去的莉諾悲傷
for the rare and radiant maiden whom the
為這位罕見而容光煥發的少女
angels named lenore
名叫勒諾的天使
nameless here forevermore
無名永遠在這裡
and this silken sad
而這絲綢般的悲傷
uncertain rustling of each purple
每個紫色的不確定的沙沙聲
curtain
窗簾
thrilled me
讓我興奮
filled me with fantastic terrors never
從來沒有讓我充滿奇異的恐懼
felt before
以前覺得
so that now
所以現在
to steal the beating of my heart i stood
為了偷走我的心跳我站著
repeating
重複
to some visitor
對一些訪客
entreating
懇求
entrance at my chamber door
我房間門口的入口
some laid visitor entreating entrance at
一些遊客在入口處
my chamber door
我的房間門
that it is
這是
and nothing more
僅此而已
presently my soul grew stronger
現在我的靈魂變得更強大
hesitating than no longer sir
猶豫比不再先生
said i or madam
我或女士說
truly your forgiveness i implore
我真的懇求你的寬恕
but the fact is i was napping
但事實是我在打盹
and so gently you came rapping
然後你輕輕地來敲擊
and so faintly you came tapping
你輕輕地敲著
tapping at my chamber door
敲我的房間門
that i scarce was sure i heard you
我幾乎確定我聽到了你的聲音
here i opened wide the door
我在這裡敞開大門
darkness there and nothing more
那裡的黑暗，僅此而已
deep into that darkness peering
在那黑暗的深處凝視
long i stood there wondering fearing
很久我站在那裡想知道害怕
doubting
懷疑
dreaming dreams no mortal ever dared to
做夢沒有凡人敢做的夢
dream before
以前做夢
but the silence was unbroken
但沉默沒有被打破
in the stillness
在寂靜中
gave no token
沒有給出任何令牌
and the only word there spoken
那裡唯一說的一句話
was the whispered word lenore
是小聲說的詞 lenore
this i whispered and an echo murmured
我低聲說這話，迴聲低語
back the word lenore
支持lenore這個詞
merely this and nothing
僅此而已
more back into the chamber turning all
更多的人回到房間裡
my soul within me burning
我的靈魂在燃燒
soon again i heard a tapping
很快我又聽到了敲擊聲
so much louder than before
比以前響亮得多
surely said i
肯定說我
surely that is something at my window
那肯定是我窗邊的東西
lattice
格子
let me see then what theoretics is
讓我看看什麼是理論
in this mystery explore
在這個神秘的探索中
let my heart be still a moment
讓我的心靜止片刻
test the wind and nothing more
試風，僅此而已
open here
在這裡打開
i flung the shutter
我扔了快門
one with many a flirting flutter
一個有很多調情的顫音
in the stepped a stately raven
在台階上，一隻莊嚴的烏鴉
of the saintly days of yore
昔日聖潔的日子
not the least obese made he
一點也不肥胖使他
not a minute stopped or stayed he
沒有一分鐘停止或停留，他
but with mine of lord or lady
但與我的主人或女士
perched above my chamber door preached
棲息在我的房門上方宣講
upon a bust of palace
在宮殿的半身像上
just above my chamber door
就在我的房間門上方
perched and sat and nothing more
棲息和坐著，僅此而已
then this ebony bird big girling my sad
然後這只烏木鳥大女孩我傷心
fancy into smiling
幻想成微笑
by the grave and stern decorum of the
以莊重嚴肅的禮儀
countenance it wore
它的表情
though thy crest be shorn and shaven
雖然你的冠被剃光
thou i said are to sure no craven
我說過你一定不會膽怯
ghastly grim an ancient raven
可怕的古老烏鴉
wandering from the nightly shore
從夜晚的岸邊徘徊
tell me what thy lordly name
告訴我你尊貴的名字
is on the night's plutonian shore
在夜晚的冥王星海岸
clothed thy raven
穿上你的烏鴉
nevermore
再也沒有
much i marveled this ungainly fowl to
我很驚訝這只笨拙的家禽
hear discourse so plainly
聽得那麼清楚
though its answer little meaning
雖然它的回答意義不大
little relevancy bore
相關性很小
for we cannot help agreeing
因為我們不得不同意
that no living human being
沒有活人
ever yet was blessed with seeing bird
曾經有幸看到鳥
above his chamber door
在他的房間門上方
bird or beast
鳥獸
such a sculptured bust
這樣雕刻的半身像
above his chamber door
在他的房間門上方
with such name
有這樣的名字
as never more
再也沒有
but the raven sitting lonely on the
但烏鴉孤獨地坐在
placid bust spoke only
平靜的胸圍只說話
that one word as of his soul and that's
那是他靈魂的一個詞，那就是
one word he did outpour
他傾訴的一句話
nothing farther
沒有更遠的了
than he uttered not a feather
比他一言不發
then he fluttered
然後他飄飄然
till i scarcely more than muttered
直到我喃喃自語
other friends
其他朋友
have flown before
以前飛過
ah
啊
sorry about that i needed to drink some
對不起，我需要喝一些
more tea
更多的茶
till i scarcely more than muttered other
直到我只是喃喃自語
friends have flown before
朋友以前飛過
on the morrow he will leave me
明天他會離開我
as my hopes have flown before then the
因為我的希望在那之前已經飛逝
bird said nevermore
鳥不再說
started at the stillness broken by reply
從回复打破的寂靜開始
sold aptly spoken doubtless said i
賣得恰如其分，毫無疑問我說
what did others
別人做了什麼
is only stock in store caught from some
只是從一些商店中捕獲的庫存
unhappy master who on merciful disaster
不幸遇難的主子
followed fast and followed faster till
跟著快，跟著快，直到
his songs one burden bore
他的歌是一個負擔
till the durges of his hope that
直到他希望
melancholy burden bore
憂鬱的負擔
of never
從來沒有
nevermore
再也沒有
i think i will stop for there uh
我想我會停在那裡
though since it is a quite the long poem
雖然因為這是一首相當長的詩
so i don't want to keep us going for too
所以我也不想讓我們繼續
long right
長右
yeah just a small quote from the raven
是的，只是烏鴉的一小段話
very beautiful poem honestly wow
老實說，非常美麗的詩哇
all right
好的
i hope you enjoyed that
我希望你喜歡
oh but i already did so many moans and
哦，但我已經做了這麼多的呻吟和
whimpers you want me to whimper more oh
嗚咽你想讓我更嗚咽 oh
how about you beg for it
你求個怎麼樣
huh
呵呵
i want to hear you back
我想听你的
that's right beg for it
這是正確的乞求
beg for it you dirty
求求你你臟
dirty little thing
骯髒的小東西
[Music]
[音樂]
hmm
唔
uh nice thank you for the donation as
嗯，謝謝你的捐贈
well such a gentle voice thank you
好溫柔的聲音謝謝
thank you so much
太感謝了
who's my precious sterling
誰是我珍貴的英鎊
who's my precious darling huh
誰是我的寶貝
is this what you wanted
這是你想要的嗎
this entire time is this what you wanted
這整個時間就是你想要的
um
嗯
[Music]
[音樂]
so so needy
太需要了
you're more needy today than usual
你今天比平時更需要幫助
good girl
好女孩
that's a good girl
這是個好女孩
good boy
好孩子
who's a good boy
誰是好孩子
that's right good boy
沒錯，好孩子
here good boy
這裡好孩子
very good boy
很好的男孩
ah
啊
i don't know if i'll whiffing would be a
我不知道我會不會聞
great idea i talked about that before
好主意，我之前說過
yeah
是的
i mean i could try
我的意思是我可以試試
[Music]
[音樂]
[Laughter]
[笑聲]
all right
好的
uh
呃
kenny thank you for the donation as well
肯尼也感謝您的捐贈
um
嗯
let's see
讓我們來看看
uh jess thank you for the ten dollars
呃，傑斯，謝謝你的十美元
welcome
歡迎
you're having a very bad day at work and
你在工作中度過了非常糟糕的一天
you almost get to cry can you say
你幾乎要哭了 你能說
something to cheer you up
讓你振作起來的東西
oh
哦
it's okay
沒關係
don't worry you're doing your best
別擔心，你正在盡力而為
you're working very hard
你很努力
ah
啊
[Music]
[音樂]
everything's going to be okay
一切都會好起來的
you should learn to be nicer to yourself
你應該學會對自己好一點
it's all right
沒關係
you're working very hard and you'll be
你工作很努力，你會的
out of there soon don't worry okay
很快就離開那裡別擔心好嗎
i love you
我愛你
keep doing your best all right darling
繼續努力吧親愛的
guilty as you're doing your best
內疚，因為你正在盡力而為
keep at it all right
堅持下去
i'm proud of you
我以你為榮
i hope that uh helps anybody that's uh
我希望你能幫助任何人
you know doing a lot right now whether
你知道現在做了很多事情
you're at work or whether you're
你在工作還是在
in school doing uh any uh
在學校做呃任何呃
anything important today
今天有什麼重要的事
can you slap me awake
你能打醒我嗎
[Music]
[音樂]
i hope that was a sufficient slap i
我希望這是一個足夠的耳光
don't know
不知道
right
正確的
you dirty dirty dirty thing wow
你骯髒骯髒的東西哇
you guys actually like that
你們真的很喜歡
disgusting
噁心
how vile how filthy
多麼卑鄙多麼骯髒
you're very embarrassing you know that
你很尷尬 你知道嗎
all right
好的
uh
呃
let me see
讓我看看
[Music]
[音樂]
god i'm so embarrassed i feel like i'm
上帝，我好尷尬，我覺得我是
so embarrassed man my face you guys
好尷尬的人，我的臉你們
can't see it right now but um
現在看不到但是嗯
i mean my ears my ears are just so red
我的意思是我的耳朵我的耳朵太紅了
ah my ears are red my ears are still red
ah 我的耳朵是紅的 我的耳朵還是紅的
what have you done what have you done
你做了什麼你做了什麼
uh you're gonna pay for that later i'll
呃，你以後會付錢的，我會的
show you who's a [ __ ] bottom
告訴你誰是 [ __ ] 底部
keep calling me bottom and see what
繼續叫我底部，看看是什麼
happens
發生
okay
好的
honestly
誠實地
if you guys have any uh recommendation
如果你們有什麼推薦
as to what else i can do i'm feel free
至於我還能做什麼，我很自由
to suggest anything i'm all ears
建議任何我都在聽的東西
honestly all right
老實說沒事
like some voice lines perhaps
也許像一些語音線
i really like that one that somebody
我真的很喜歡那個人
recommended
推薦的
[Music]
[音樂]
what are you doing around here by
你在這附近做什麼
yourself walking into such dangerous
自己走進這麼危險的地方
territory huh
領地啊
thank you for the telenation as well uh
謝謝你的電話，嗯
appreciated the oh was it this
感謝哦，是不是這個
five dollar donation thank you for the
五美元的捐款謝謝你
five dollar donation
五美元捐款
okay
好的
sounds bottom all right well
聽起來不錯
can't win
贏不了
there you just can't win some of these
在那裡你無法贏得其中一些
uh battles i guess
呃戰鬥我猜
oh hold on give me a second guys
哦，等等，給我第二個伙計們
my goodness
我的天啊
degrading
有辱人格的
the burger king footlot oh my goodness
哦，我的天哪，漢堡王
you really want me to say that out of
你真的想讓我這麼說
all things out of anything you came here
一切源於你來到這裡
you want to recommend the burger king
你想推薦漢堡王
foot lettuce meme in in this chat right
在這個聊天中加入生菜模因吧
now
現在
i don't think so
我不這麼認為
even though i it's it's very funny but i
即使我很有趣，但我
don't think i could i can i i don't
不認為我能 我能 我不能
think i can bring myself to muster the
認為我可以讓自己鼓起
courage and and uh strength and
勇氣和 呃 力量和
willpower to say such things right now
現在說出這樣的話的意志力
in front of all you guys
在你們所有人面前
you want me to say the goro voice line
你要我說五郎語音線
goro voice line wow i like how it's a
goro 語音線哇，我喜歡它的樣子
people know it's the whimper one
人們知道這是嗚咽的人
don't know where it is
不知道在哪裡
i don't think i can find the uh the
我不認為我能找到呃
actual you know dialogue for it where is
實際上你知道它的對話在哪裡
it
它
yeah i don't think i can find it sorry
是的，我不認為我能找到它對不起
i did on my tick tock i know i did but i
我做了我的滴答聲我知道我做了，但我
just can't i don't remember where it is
只是我不記得它在哪裡
i wrote it down somewhere but uh it's
我把它寫在某個地方，但呃，它是
gone now it's all
現在已經過去了
oh please take your meds by the way okay
哦，順便吃藥好嗎
um please remember to take your meds and
嗯，請記得吃藥
take care of yourself guys
照顧好自己的傢伙
don't make me worry so much
別讓我這麼擔心
please don't make me worry so much
請不要讓我這麼擔心
also good morning
早上好
good morning darling
早上好親愛的
talk in spanish
用西班牙語說話
i don't really know too much
我真的不知道太多
to say in spanish other than just
用西班牙語說不僅僅是
uh
呃
what else
還有什麼
yeah i don't think i know anything else
是的，我想我什麼都不知道
sorry
對不起
my
我的
you quit that you quit that oh i'll bite
你放棄了，你放棄了，哦，我會咬人的
your ear i swear
我發誓你的耳朵
all right
好的
oh
哦
kazu thank you for the donation
kazu 謝謝你的捐贈
you just woke up from a nightmare can
你剛從噩夢中醒來
you say something to make you feel
你說些什麼讓你感覺
better
更好的
don't worry
別擔心
don't worry everything's okay now
別擔心，現在一切都好
so needy but
如此需要，但
you're safe now
你現在安全了
it's just the dream just a bad nightmare
這只是一場噩夢
okay
好的
it's not real none of it was real
這不是真的
that's it that's all right
就是這樣，沒關係
good
好的
good boy
好孩子
good girl
好女孩
back to sleep okay
回去睡覺好了
you have a big day tomorrow so
你明天有大日子所以
don't want to be too sleepy in the
不想在裡面太困
morning for that
早上那個
i'll get up early and make you breakfast
我會早起給你做早餐
all right
好的
you don't have to worry about it
你不必擔心
that's it
而已
good job
好工作
good girl
好女孩
that's a good girl
這是個好女孩
hmm
唔
sleep well okay
睡個好覺
good night
晚安
good night darling
晚安親愛的
thank you for the ten dollars and uh
謝謝你的十美元，呃
dire thank you for the dollar as well
也非常感謝你的美元
what is this
這是什麼
why why does that look like a jojo
為什麼看起來像jojo
reference
參考
oh right for some of the people that
哦，對某些人來說是正確的
didn't come by already i guess i can
還沒來，我想我可以
i guess i can uh
我想我可以
oh sorry about that
哦，對不起
i guess i can uh really put my
我想我真的可以把我的
chest to my microphone again
再次對著我的麥克風
just one more time
就再一次
all right
好的
i hope that was audible
我希望那是可以聽到的
uh
呃
i tried to do it on the other ear till
我試著在另一隻耳朵上做，直到
it's on the other side but uh i did my
它在另一邊，但我做了我的
best
最好的
i did my best
我盡力了
and so did you you guys are doing your
你們也是這樣嗎？
best till
最好到
each and every one of you are doing the
你們每個人都在做
best that you can
盡你所能
oh uh
哦哦
cage thank you for the 20
籠子謝謝你的20
soft dom
軟域
uh what are some
呃，有什麼
what are some
有什麼
nice uh
不錯哦
trigger
扳機
like
喜歡
things that people like from asmr i
人們喜歡 asmr i 的東西
don't really know many
真的不知道很多
yeah i don't really know many that i can
是的，我真的不知道很多我可以
try
嘗試
oh hey there lady
哦，嘿，女士
hey there pretty lady
嘿，漂亮的女士
i wonder if i can
我想知道我能不能
cover your ears
摀住耳朵
like this
像這樣
on i wonder if uh
我想知道如果呃
brushing against the microphone you said
刷你說的麥克風
oh my goodness all right
哦，天哪，好吧
what is that i don't know i think that
那是什麼我不知道我認為
was i just i just grabbed my uh my
難道我只是我抓住了我的呃我的
pokemon and rubbed it against it yeah
口袋妖怪和它摩擦它是的
um
嗯
a lot of you guys recommended blowing
很多人建議吹
but uh
但是呃
did that tickle
有沒有撓痒癢
um
嗯
blow more aggressively oh okay
吹得更猛哦好吧
[Music]
[音樂]
good that's really good
很好，真的很好 1835年
okay
好的 1836年
it tickles you said
你說的很癢
you know that's what else we'll tickle
你知道這就是我們會撓痒癢的 1838年
uh give me a second i think i do want to
呃，給我一秒鐘，我想我確實想
try uh
試試看
having
有
one more snack
再來一份小吃
um
嗯 1843年
ah
啊 1844年
what's it i have
我有什麼 1845年
just some pretzels that's all
只是一些椒鹽脆餅而已 1846年
good girl
好女孩 1847年
that's a very good girl
這是一個很好的女孩 1848年
good boy who's a good boy
好孩子誰是好孩子
that's my boy
這是我的男孩
head pats
拍頭
i don't know if i can deal proper uh
我不知道我能不能處理得當呃 1854年
head prep but
頭部準備但是 1855年
um oh alexis thank you for the donation
嗯哦，亞歷克西斯謝謝你的捐贈 1856年
you've been really having a hard time
你真的很難過 1857年
and want to cry all day
想哭一整天 1858年
and uh listening to you makes me feel
嗯，聽你說話讓我覺得
better you don't want to request
最好你不想要求
anything you just want to know how much
任何你只想知道多少
you had an effect on my life also your
你對我的生活也有影響 1862年
heartbeat is really soothing love you
心跳真的很舒緩愛你 1863年
thank you for the donation and uh
謝謝你的捐贈，呃 1864年
i really do hope that
我真的希望 1865年
um even if a little bit my silly chewing
嗯即使有點我的愚蠢咀嚼 1866年
or uh drinking of my tea or
或者呃喝我的茶或者 1867年
stupid uh earlix help uh
愚蠢的呃earlix幫助呃 1868年
have helped make you feel better i'm
幫助你感覺更好
just a silly boy but um
只是一個傻男孩，但是嗯
the fact that you guys are here and
你們在這裡的事實
willing to listen to this and uh you
願意聽這個和你 1872年
know
知道 1873年
try this out with me for the first time
第一次和我一起試試 1874年
it means a lot so thank you
這意味著很多，所以謝謝 1875年
thank you for coming by and
謝謝你的光臨和 1876年
thank you for being here
非常感謝您的到來 1877年
you all are very sweet
你們都很甜蜜 1878年
very very sweet
非常非常甜 1879年
uh oh ting thank you for the four
嗯，哦，婷，謝謝你的四個
dollars
美元
you want me to read more poems and
你想讓我讀更多的詩和 1882年
stories
故事 1883年
you really like it when i read poems you
你真的很喜歡我讀詩你 1884年
guys like it when i read the poems and
當我讀詩和 1885年
stuff
東西 1886年
i don't know what that means but uh
我不知道那是什麼意思但是呃 1887年
where is that from i really don't know
那是從哪裡來的，我真的不知道 1888年
where that was from
那是從哪裡來的
oh what is from jiu-jitsu
哦，柔術是什麼
huh
呵呵 1891年
i don't even know if i pronounce that
我什至不知道我是否發音 1892年
correctly but okay
正確但沒關係 1893年
i'll consider doing uh
我會考慮做呃 1894年
i'll do more uh what's it poems or
我會做更多呃這是什麼詩或 1895年
stories in the future oh it's from a
未來的故事哦，它來自一個 1896年
tick tock all right
滴答滴答 1897年
okay all right go to all right koto
好的 好的 去 好的 koto 1898年
can you say this voice slime
你能說這個聲音嗎 史萊姆
uh
呃
what is this
這是什麼
is this from jojo it is from jojo
這是jojo寄來的嗎？jojo寄來的
eyes of heaven
天眼 1903年
i have not watched anything jojo so this
我什麼都沒看過jojo所以這個 1904年
is like i i feel like i either said
就像我覺得我要么說 1905年
something that was a complete meme or it
這是一個完整的模因或它 1906年
was just something that's like entirely
只是完全一樣的東西 1907年
out of context i have no idea what is
斷章取義，我不知道是什麼 1908年
the eyes of heaven huh
天堂之眼hh 1909年
what the heck is eyes of heaven
天眼是什麼鬼
but to be honest hey guys
但老實說，嘿伙計們
be sure to focus on your work okay don't
一定要專注於你的工作，好吧，不要 1912年
uh don't fixate too much on what's going
呃不要太關注正在發生的事情 1913年
on with uh with me right now
現在就和我在一起 1914年
i'm just trying to make sure you guys
我只是想確保你們 1915年
are comforted and
得到安慰和 1916年
make sure that your day is even if the
確保你的一天是即使 1917年
little bit
一點 1918年
just a tad better if anything
如果有的話，會更好一點 1919年
please
請
just focus on your work
只專注於你的工作 1921年
don't compromise your well-being for me
不要為了我損害你的幸福 1922年
and take care of yourselves
並照顧好自己 1923年
okay i care about like about you a lot
好吧，我很在乎你 1924年
okay
好的 1925年
today is your birthday oh thank you for
今天是你的生日哦謝謝你 1926年
the donation and uh happy birthday
捐贈和呃生日快樂 1927年
happy birthday to you
祝你生日快樂 1928年
i hope you have a good one buddy okay
我希望你有一個好夥伴好嗎
come on
快點 1931年
ah
啊 1932年
i hope the swallow noises don't bother
我希望燕子的聲音不會打擾 1933年
anybody
任何人 1934年
cause uh yeah i do need to drink my i
因為嗯，是的，我確實需要喝我的我 1935年
drink my wawa my water
喝我的哇哇我的水 1936年
make sure my throat is nice and healthy
確保我的喉嚨健康 1937年
can i be more possessive again
我可以再擁有更多的佔有欲嗎 1938年
i don't know what i would even say
我什至不知道我會說什麼 1939年
if to be uh more possessive huh
如果要呃佔有欲更強的話
where the hell do you think you're
你以為你在哪裡 1941年
going you're not going anywhere
去你哪兒也不去 1942年
you're mine
你是我的 1943年
and mine alone
和我一個人 1944年
okay
好的 1945年
it's like uh yandere levels
這就像呃yandere級別 1946年
of possession
佔有的 1947年
i don't think i can say that one i saw
我想我不能說我看到的那個 1948年
it in the chat but i don't know if i can
它在聊天中，但我不知道我是否可以 1949年
see that without
看到沒有
making myself like recede into my own uh
讓自己像退縮到我自己的呃 1951年
you know shirt like a turtle
你知道襯衫像烏龜 1952年
oh my goodness wow
哦，天哪，哇 1953年
a british accent a british accent
英國口音 英國口音 1954年
what
什麼 1955年
i don't think i can
我不認為我可以 1956年
uh not right now
呃，現在不行 1957年
without uh you know making fun of uh the
沒有呃你知道取笑呃 1958年
entire
全部的 1959年
entirety of
全部
britain but i mean i feel like we do
英國，但我的意思是我覺得我們喜歡 1961年
that all the time right now honestly
老實說，現在一直都是 1962年
uh
呃 1963年
where are you going
你要去哪裡 1964年
why don't you stay here with me for a
你為什麼不和我一起待在這裡 1965年
little while longer
再過一會兒 1966年
okay
好的 1967年
little kitty
小貓咪 1968年
thank you for the toenail and uh hope
謝謝你的腳趾甲，嗯希望
that was uh hope that was good enough
那是呃希望那已經足夠好了
uh simo mall thank you for the three
呃 simo mall 謝謝你的三個 1971年
dollars
美元 1972年
and uh millie thank you for the two
嗯，米莉，謝謝你們兩個 1973年
again i don't know if i'm saying that
我不知道我是不是在說那個 1975年
correctly
正確地 1976年
it means sister
是姐姐的意思 1977年
oh
哦 1978年
sister
姐姐
but why why do you want me to call you
但是你為什麼要我給你打電話
all right
好的 1982年
okay
1983年
you would like me to read a richard
你想讓我讀一個理查德 1984年
silken poem
絲綢詩 1985年
a richard silken poem huh
一首理查德絲綢詩 1986年
i got honestly i don't read many poems
老實說，我讀的詩不多 1987年
so you guys are like opening my eyes to
所以你們就像打開我的眼睛 1988年
a lot of uh different i don't know
很多不同的我不知道
like
喜歡
i know a lot of people have read uh
我知道很多人讀過
what's it i read uh
我讀的是什麼
the raven but i guess i was one of those
烏鴉，但我想我是其中之一
uh
呃
one of those boys that managed to not
那些設法不
read it and uh in school so hey
讀它，呃在學校，所以嘿
okay
好的
uh link thank you for the donation can
呃鏈接謝謝你的捐贈可以
you say this for fun
你這麼說是為了好玩
[Laughter]
[笑聲]
sure i can oh i like this hold on
當然我可以哦我喜歡這個堅持下去 2001年
macaroni
通心粉 2002年
with the chicken strips
配雞肉條 2003年
[Laughter]
[笑聲] 2004年
um
嗯 2005年
why
為什麼 2006年
all right
好的 2007年
well i mean
我的意思是 2008年
there you go sir
先生，你去吧
oh man the power
哦，男人的力量
man asmr is powerful man
man asmr 是強大的人
i really want to hear what that sounds
我真的很想听聽這聽起來是什麼
like
喜歡
god
上帝
also uh and thank you for the tony you
也謝謝你的托尼
want me to call you balbay
要我叫你巴爾貝 2016 年
of course
當然
my balbae
我的巴爾巴
balbay
巴爾貝
balba
巴爾巴
pumpkin
南瓜
darling
寵兒
baby
嬰兒
honey
蜜糖
sweetie
甜心
darling
寵兒
you're so good today darling
你今天真好，親愛的
very good
很好
balban
巴爾班
um
嗯
uh
呃
okay
好的
oh and uh donut thank you for the
哦，嗯，甜甜圈謝謝你
donation as well
捐贈也
thank you for the asmr stream showball
謝謝你的 asmr 流表演
uh your self-voice really makes you feel
呃你的自我聲音真的讓你覺得
like sleeping on the marshmallow sorry
就像睡在棉花糖上
your english is not good you'll try to
你的英語不好你會努力的
study harder in school it's totally fine
在學校努力學習 完全沒問題
you don't have to
你不必
you guys i appreciate it it feels really
你們，我很感激這感覺真的
lovely that's uh
可愛的，嗯
learning a different language for the
學習不同的語言
sake of somebody else will never not be
永遠不會為別人著想
something
某物
that i appreciate a lot like
我很感激
so many people do that just so that they
很多人這樣做只是為了讓他們
can talk to the ones that they love and
可以和他們愛的人交談
uh it's something really sweet
嗯，真的很甜
i really do uh love it a ton when uh you
我真的很喜歡你
know
知道
you just want to
你只想
like i want to do that too so i can talk
就像我也想那樣，所以我可以說話
to more of you guys and a lot other
對你們中的更多人和許多其他人
people
人們
it's very sweet and very
它很甜很
endearing
可愛的
i think that's what it's called right
我認為這就是所謂的正確
smooches are like tiny kisses
接吻就像小吻
vessels
船隻
xv thank you for the
xv 謝謝你
donation
捐款
ayo for free hey yo
ayo免費嘿喲
for free have a nice day
免費祝您有美好的一天
and um may you're the first gamer i've
嗯，你可能是我第一個玩遊戲的人
ever enjoyed in the reason i got into
曾經享受過我進入的原因
twitch a couple days ago this is my
幾天前抽搐這是我的
first donation ever so you please say
有史以來第一次捐款，所以請說
okay
好的
i don't
我不
know what is that where's that from i
知道那是什麼 我從哪裡來的
feel it feels familiar
感覺很熟悉
all right
好的
oh it's from
哦，它來自
oh my god right it is you guys are you
哦，我的上帝，對，你們是你們
guys are very right yeah
伙計們非常正確，是的
uh oh yeah thank you for the 521 gift
哦哦是的謝謝你的521禮物
subs hope you're having a good day and
潛艇希望你有一個美好的一天
uh good morning
早上好
uh paige thank you for the uh very
呃佩奇非常感謝你
generous donation as well this is very
慷慨的捐贈，這是非常
comforting to listen to while you're
安慰你的時候聽
writing are you able to say a very light
寫作你能說的很輕嗎
or domestic type
或國內型
my darling or my dear
我親愛的
my dear
親愛的
my darling
我的寶貝
uh not thank you for the six dollars um
呃不謝謝你的六美元
just wants to thank you for all that you
只是想感謝你所做的一切
do and all that you bring me and so many
做你帶給我的一切，還有這麼多
other people so much comfort make sure
其他人這麼多的安慰確保
you take care of yourself every time you
你每次都照顧好自己
hear polaroid love you think of me
聽到寶麗來愛你想起我
that's really sweet
這真的很甜蜜
that's really really sweet
真的很甜
guys
伙計們
you guys are so so adorable tonight
你們今晚真可愛
i don't know
我不知道
i don't think i can not control myself
我不認為我無法控制自己
okay
好的
can you say
你可以說
uh
呃
is that i say it correctly
是我說對了嗎
[Music]
[音樂]
i hope i said that correctly uh
我希望我說的沒錯
that's the one for uh cantonese right
那是呃廣東話的權利
okay
好的
i do want to uh probably wrap this up in
我確實想，呃，可能把它包起來
a little bit since i am
一點點，因為我是
running out of
快用完
iomedu
約梅杜
oh
哦
[Music]
[音樂]
oh no
不好了
okay
好的
okay okay that's all that's all you guys
好吧好吧，這就是你們的全部
get
得到
that's all you guys get
這就是你們得到的全部
embarrassing
尷尬
i'm embarrassing as [ __ ] all right
我很尷尬 [ __ ] 好吧
so uh yeah
所以，是的
um i will have to wrap this up uh in a
嗯，我得把它包起來
bit
少量
since um i am running out of ideas or
因為嗯，我已經沒有想法了，或者
things to say but for real if you guys
要說的話，但如果你們是真的
like this please let me know like um
像這樣請讓我知道
all the all the support tonight and uh
今晚所有的支持和呃
just like hearing your feedback really
就像真的聽到你的反饋一樣
does mean a lot and uh i do might i
確實意味著很多，嗯，我可能會
might want to try this again next time
下次可能想再試一次
since uh
自從呃
it's something new and something i've
這是新的東西，我有的東西
never done before so uh
以前沒做過所以呃
it's
它是
ah
啊
i really wanna
我真的很想
try it again i'd say yeah try it again
再試一次，我會說是的，再試一次
and uh
呃
bring something else to the table that
把別的東西帶到桌子上
might be uh kind of nice right
可能很好，對吧
it's really embarrassing but i'm glad
這真的很尷尬，但我很高興
you like it i'm glad you really like it
你喜歡我很高興你真的很喜歡
uh amber thank you for the five dollars
嗯琥珀謝謝你的五美元
uh
呃
i feel like you have no power to do your
我覺得你沒有權力做你的
work taking please say
工作請說
you better go do your work now otherwise
你最好現在就去做你的工作，否則
i'll stop talking to you
我不再和你說話了
if you go do it now then maybe i'll give
如果你現在就去做，那麼也許我會給
you a few more kisses as a reward
你多親幾個吻作為獎勵
i hope that was enough for you
我希望這對你來說已經足夠了
uh also errols thank you for the big
呃也謝謝你的大
donation this is the first stream i've
捐贈這是我的第一個流
ever been able to catch live and you're
曾經能夠現場直播，而你
thoroughly enjoying the experience it's
徹底享受這種體驗
been a rough time lately can get some
最近很艱難，可以得到一些
deep breathing and praise please
請深呼吸和讚美
um
嗯
you're doing so good
你做得很好
[Music]
[音樂]
good job
好工作
very good job
幹得漂亮
i'm proud of you
我以你為榮
i hope that was good enough
我希望這已經足夠好了
it sounds like uh you know something
聽起來你知道些什麼
cute and cuddly right
可愛又惹人憐愛
you owe me a quote a line from kingdom
你欠我一句來自王國的台詞
hearts what is this from kingdom hearts
王國之心這是什麼
wow what a game
哇什麼遊戲
a scattered dream
散落的夢
that's like a far off memory
就像遙遠的記憶
a far off memory that's like a scattered
遙遠的記憶就像散落的
dream i want to line the pieces up
夢想我想把碎片排列起來
yours
你的
and mine
和我的
i hope that satisfied you
我希望你滿意
still never really played uh still never
還沒有真正玩過 呃 從來沒有
really played many kingdom hearts games
真的玩了很多王國之心遊戲
but wow
但是哇
yeah
是的
i think the only one i ever played was
我想我唯一玩過的是
uh 365 days
呃 365 天
on the diaz
在迪亞茲
really thank you for the twenty dollars
真的謝謝你的二十美元
just wanna say you sound really cute
只想說你聽起來很可愛
when speaking chinese oh
說中文的時候哦
thank you so much
太感謝了
i sound cute i'm trying my best when i
我聽起來很可愛，當我努力的時候
try to
嘗試
when i try to uh pronounce uh enunciate
當我嘗試 uh 發音 uh enunciate
everything
一切
uh assa thank you for the donation as
呃 assa 謝謝你的捐贈
well and um
嗯，嗯
thank you for the donation maybe a
謝謝你的捐贈
heartbeat asmr to finish of course
heartbeat asmr 當然要完成
any anything for you darling
親愛的，有什麼給你的
um
嗯
all right
好的
oh my goodness are the chats moving so
哦，我的天哪，聊天是這樣移動的
fast i couldn't see uh some of the
很快我看不到呃一些
comments from earlier
之前的評論
everybody wants me to say the scatter
每個人都希望我說分散
mooch line i don't know what that is
mooch line 我不知道那是什麼
what is the scar moosh line
什麼是疤痕哞哞線
itadakimasu
板棣馬須
a
一種
uh oh
哦哦
before you wrap it up can you do the
在你結束之前你能做到嗎
sound you made when you stretched
伸展時發出的聲音
earlier again it was really cute what i
早些時候，我真的很可愛
didn't sound when i stretched
我伸展的時候沒有聲音
ah
啊
like that
像那樣
yeah i hope that was okay
是的，我希望沒關係
also stephanie thank you for the big
斯蒂芬妮也謝謝你的大
donation as well my goodness
捐贈以及我的天哪
um congrats to you for achieving such a
嗯，恭喜你取得了這樣的成績
great goal you are super popular in
你超級受歡迎的偉大目標
china we love you you know that you are
中國 我們愛你 你知道你是
beloved all around the world and you
全世界都愛你和你
deserve this
值得這個
that's why i want to do my best for all
這就是為什麼我想為所有人做到最好
of you guys in the future and uh
你們的未來和呃
that's why i've been trying to stream at
這就是為什麼我一直在嘗試流式傳輸
like different times so that other
喜歡不同的時間，所以其他
people around the world can watch me so
全世界的人都可以看著我
i'm glad that
我很高興
that's recognized and i'm really glad
這是公認的，我真的很高興
that you guys uh
那你們
not just my people in uh
不只是我在呃的人
in the united states but everybody
在美國，但每個人
around the world likes to watch and
全世界都喜歡看和
support me it's really precious and
支持我真的很珍貴
sweet so thank you
好甜，謝謝
i'll never take your guys support for
我永遠不會接受你們的支持
granted it means a lot and
授予它意味著很多，
i'll continue to carry all of that until
我將繼續攜帶所有這些直到
the very end
最後
along this wonderful journey that we're
沿著這美妙的旅程，我們
having together so far
到目前為止在一起
yeah and sometimes i think about all the
是的，有時我會想到所有
support you guys give me and uh i wonder
支持你們給我，嗯，我想知道
like
喜歡
if i'm really
如果我真的
doing enough to you know meet your
做的足夠你知道滿足你的
expectations but
期望但
and now every single time we stream like
現在每次我們流式傳輸
you guys prove me
你們證明了我
prove to me that
向我證明
i am
我是
very well worth your time
非常值得你花時間
and your uh
和你的呃
and your support so thank you
和你的支持，謝謝
for not only uh making me feel better
不僅讓我感覺更好
but uh
但是呃
for making me feel validated in that
讓我覺得在這方面得到了認可
sense
感覺
i love you guys so much
我非常愛你們
thank you
謝謝
thank you so much
太感謝了
uh i love my guildies i love my guilties
呃，我愛我的罪孽 我愛我的罪孽
saltball can you please say
鹽球你能說嗎
ah
啊
well
好吧
hold on let me drink some more water
等等，讓我再喝點水
kind of thirsty right now
現在有點渴
i think
我想
that'll be it for today though i don't
今天就這樣了，雖然我沒有
think
思考
i really have anything else that's all i
我真的有什麼其他的
want to try out but i really appreciate
想試試，但我真的很感激
all your guys's time and your company
你所有的時間和你的公司
for today i know it's it's already been
今天我知道它已經是
two hours and it didn't even feel like
兩個小時，甚至感覺不到
two hours right
兩個小時吧
wow
哇
uh
呃
it means a lot that so many of you came
很多人來了，這意味著很多
by today to listen and uh show your
到今天為止，聽你展示你的
support so
這麼支持
i'll see you tomorrow morning or uh in
明天早上見
about
關於
i'd say in about
我會說大約
10 hours from now or 11 hours from now
10 小時後或 11 小時後
we're going to be playing some uh
我們會玩一些呃
morphin f
嗎啡
i'm going to try out a final pizzeria
我要試試最後一家比薩店
simulator in the morning so i hope you
早上模擬器，所以我希望你
guys are excited for that another horror
伙計們為另一個恐怖事件感到興奮
game
遊戲
and then i will take sunday off to plan
然後我會在星期天休假計劃
out the next week coming by
下週即將到來
can you sing kind of a lullaby before
你能先唱一首搖籃曲嗎
you end stream tonight make sure you
你今晚結束直播確保你
rest well
好好休息
uh
呃
hold on
堅持，稍等
have you guys listened to my music box
你們聽過我的音樂盒嗎
before i got a i don't know if this will
在我得到 ai 之前不知道這是否會
sound fine but hopefully it's not too
聽起來不錯，但希望不是太
loud you just reminded me when you said
大聲你只是提醒我當你說
uh
呃
when you said uh
當你說呃
lullaby
催眠曲
[Music]
[音樂]
do
做
yeah it's uh close to you um i guess i
是的，它離你很近，嗯，我想我
can hum that one more time for uh for
可以再哼一次 uh for
all you guys right
你們都對
hey
嘿
[Music]
[音樂]
me
我
is
是
okay that's enough
好吧，這就夠了
i hope that's a good enough lullaby for
我希望這是一個足夠好的搖籃曲
you
你
uh really thank you for the donation uh
呃真的謝謝你的捐贈
everything for the donation just want to
捐贈的一切只想
tell you how much i love you the time we
告訴你我們有多愛你
spent with you are always so precious to
和你一起度過總是那麼珍貴
me please have a good rest after this
之後請好好休息
it means have a sweet dream oh you have
這意味著有一個甜蜜的夢哦，你有
a sweet dream too
也是一個甜蜜的夢
i hope i said that correctly
我希望我說得對
you're so
你是如此
uh cute my precious boy but you did so
嗯，可愛的我寶貝，但你這樣做了
well just let you know you're always
好吧，只是讓你知道你總是
here by your side and we'll keep
在你身邊，我們會一直保持
supporting you you deserve all the love
支持你你值得所有的愛
and thank you for the asmr and have a
謝謝你的 asmr 並有一個
good rest after streaming love you thank
流媒體後好好休息愛你謝謝
you for the donation akiko
你為捐贈 akiko
have a good night too and uh take care
也祝你有個美好的夜晚，呃保重
okay thanks for coming by guys
好的，謝謝你們的到來
i'll leave you off of one more thing
我會讓你再做一件事
before we end it off here all right
在我們在這裡結束之前
i i like that you're biting it just
我喜歡你只是在咬它
seems so cute
看起來很可愛
all right that's enough bye bye
好吧，這就夠了，再見
ah
啊
that's it's embarrassing as [ __ ] god
這就是 [ __ ] 上帝的尷尬
take care everybody and thank you for
照顧好每個人，謝謝你
coming by to my first
來到我的第一個
asmr stream it was uh it was really fun
asmr 流，嗯，真的很有趣
to get to try this out and i'm glad
嘗試一下，我很高興
everybody liked it as much as they did
每個人都和他們一樣喜歡它
we might try this again in the future so
我們將來可能會再試一次，所以
uh keep your eyes out and uh keep your
uh 保持你的眼睛，uh 保持你的
ears open for uh more asmr content in
為更多的 asmr 內容打開耳朵
the future okay
未來還好
i love you guys a lot
我非常愛你們
rest well and i'll see you next time
好好休息，下次見
bye bye
再見
good night
晚安
have a good day
祝你有美好的一天
take care all right
好好照顧
okay
好的
now
現在
let me close out of all
讓我關閉所有
this
這
and
和
check my dm
檢查我的 dm
i alm oh my god i almost forgot to end
我天啊，我差點忘了結束
right
正確的
that's the button i have to press i had
那是我必須按下的按鈕
to click stop streaming i did i almost
點擊停止流媒體，我幾乎做到了
forgot to press that oh my god that
忘了按那個哦，天哪
would have been so embarrassing all
會很尷尬
right good night take care bye
對了晚安保重再見
bye
再見
you
你